
        <root>
        <kyero>
            <feed_version>3</feed_version>
        </kyero><property>
             <id>1070</id>
            <date>2025-01-09 09:38:25</date>
            <ref>4129</ref>
            <price>310000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Apartment</type>
            <town>Orihuela</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.928569000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.746657000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Orihuela Costa</location_detail>
            <beds>2</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>1</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>80</built>
                <plot>44</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>D</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/apartments/tid4129</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/apartamentos/tid4129</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/appartements/tid4129</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/kvartiry/tid4129</ru>
            </url><virtual_tour_url>https://app.cloudpano.com/tours/o1CSMOpuV?disable=logo</virtual_tour_url><desc><es>Moderno apartamento en Jardines de Montesolana, Orihuela Costa.
Apartamento distribuido en dos habitaciones y dos baños. Dispone de un amplio salón-comedor con cocina americana y acceso directo al amplio jardín de 43m2 con vistas a las zonas comunes del residencial con orientación sur. Se encuentra en la urbanización de Jardines de Montesolana que dispone de piscina comunitaria y zonas ajardinadas. 

Este residencial se encuentra cerca del Centro Comercial La Zenia Boulevard (Orihuela Costa). La Zenia está cerca de Cabo Roig, Campoamor y Playa Flamenca. Se trata de una zona de cultivo, cerca de todas las comodidades y el famoso centro comercial La Zenia Boulevard. A pocos minutos de la N -332 y la autopista del Mediterráneo AP-7 en dirección Alicante y Cartagena. También existen alrededor de los campos de golf de Villamartín, Las Ramblas, Campoamor y Las Colinas.</es><en>Modern apartment in Jardines de Montesolana, Orihuela Costa.
This partment distributed in two bedrooms and two bathrooms. It has a spacious living-dining room with open plan kitchen and direct access to the large garden of 43 m2 with views to the communal areas of the residential with south orientation. It is located in the Jardines de Montesolana development which has a communal swimming pool and garden areas. 

This residential is close to La Zenia Boulevard shopping centre (Orihuela Costa). La Zenia is close to Cabo Roig, Campoamor and Playa Flamenca. It is a growing area, close to all amenities and the famous La Zenia Boulevard shopping centre. Only a few minutes from the N-332 and the Mediterranean motorway AP-7 towards Alicante and Cartagena. There are also around the golf courses of Villamartin, Las Ramblas, Campoamor and Las Colinas.
</en><fr>Appartement moderne à Jardines de Montesolana, Orihuela Costa.
Appartement distribué en deux chambres et deux salles de bains. Il dispose d'un salon-salle à manger spacieux avec cuisine ouverte et accès direct au grand jardin de 43m2 avec vue sur les zones communes de la résidence avec orientation sud. Il est situé dans le lotissement Jardines de Montesolana qui dispose d'une piscine commune et de zones de jardin. 

Cette résidence est proche du centre commercial La Zenia Boulevard (Orihuela Costa). La Zenia est proche de Cabo Roig, Campoamor et Playa Flamenca. Il s'agit d'une zone en pleine expansion, proche de toutes les commodités et du célèbre centre commercial La Zenia Boulevard. À quelques minutes de la N-332 et de l'autoroute méditerranéenne AP-7 en direction d'Alicante et de Carthagène. Les terrains de golf de Villamartin, Las Ramblas, Campoamor et Las Colinas se trouvent également à proximité.
</fr><ru>Современные апартаменты в районе Жардинес-де-Монтесолана, Ориуэла-Коста.
Апартаменты состоят из двух спален и двух ванных комнат. Просторная гостиная-столовая с кухней открытого плана и прямым выходом в большой сад площадью 43m2 с видом на коммунальные зоны жилого комплекса с южной ориентацией. Он расположен в комплексе Jardines de Montesolana, где есть общий бассейн и садовые зоны. 

Жилой комплекс находится недалеко от торгового центра La Zenia Boulevard (Ориуэла-Коста). Ла-Зения находится недалеко от Кабо-Роиг, Кампоамор и Плайя Фламенка. Это растущий район, рядом со всеми удобствами и знаменитым торговым центром La Zenia Boulevard. Всего в нескольких минутах езды от шоссе N-332 и средиземноморской автомагистрали AP-7, ведущей в Аликанте и Картахену. Также рядом находятся поля для гольфа в Вилламартине, Лас-Рамбласе, Кампоаморе и Лас-Колинасе.</ru></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 0 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 0</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: 2000</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_1.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_2.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_3.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_4.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_5.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_6.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_7.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_8.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_9.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_10.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_11.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_12.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_13.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_14.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_15.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_16.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_17.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_18.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_19.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_20.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_21.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_22.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_23.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_24.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_25.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_26.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4129/4129_27.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>1053</id>
            <date>2025-01-09 09:36:13</date>
            <ref>4142</ref>
            <price>597800</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Apartment</type>
            <town>Pilar de la Horadada</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.867639105700</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.765104718400</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Torre de la Horadada</location_detail>
            <beds>4</beds><baths>3</baths><pool>1</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>120</built>
                <plot>120</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>X</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/apartments/tid4142</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/apartamentos/tid4142</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/appartements/tid4142</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/kvartiry/tid4142</ru>
            </url><virtual_tour_url>https://api.bennecke.com/p/embed/4142</virtual_tour_url><desc><es>Espacioso bungalow en planta baja en Torre de la Horadada. Esta moderna vivienda con orientación sur, cuenta con 4 habitaciones, 3 baños, un amplio salón-comedor con cocina americana y acceso directo a la terraza y jardín de 120m2. Se encuentra en el complejo donde se puede disfrutar piscina comunitaria y zonas ajardinadas. 

Torre de la Horadada es una zona prestigiosa de la Costa Blanca, muy próxima a Mil Palmeras, Campoamor, San Pedro del Pintar y Orihuela Costa. Solamente en 10 minutos se puede llegar a las famosas lagunas de sal de San Pedro del Pinatar y centro balneario marino Thalasia. Pilar De La Horadada, disfruta de más de 2500 horas de sol al año y temperatura media de 18ºC, que lo convierte en una zona privilegiada. Cuenta con una amplia zona de servicios, zonas verdes, paseos marítimos y puerto deportivo. A tan solo 5 minutos de los centros comerciales La Zenia Boulevard y Dos Mares. A estas magníficas condiciones climatológicas se unen playas de arena tales como la Playa Jesuitas, Playa del Puerto y Playa de las Higuericas. Bien comunicada con la carretera nacional N-332 y a la autopista del mediterráneo AP-7. Cercana a grandes ciudades como Murcia y Alicante.</es><en>Spacious ground floor bungalow in Torre de la Horadada. This modern south facing property has 4 bedrooms, 3 bathrooms, a spacious living-dining room with open plan kitchen and direct access to the terrace and garden of 120m2. It is located in the complex where you can enjoy communal pool and garden areas. 

Torre de la Horadada is a prestigious area of the Costa Blanca, very close to Mil Palmeras, Campoamor, San Pedro del Pintar and Orihuela Costa. The famous salt lagoons of San Pedro del Pinatar and the Thalasia marine spa centre can be reached in only 10 minutes. Pilar De La Horadada, enjoys more than 2500 hours of sunshine a year and an average temperature of 18ºC, which makes it a privileged area. It has a wide range of services, green areas, promenades and a marina. Just 5 minutes from the shopping centres La Zenia Boulevard and Dos Mares. In addition to these magnificent weather conditions, there are sandy beaches such as Playa Jesuitas, Playa del Puerto and Playa de las Higuericas. Well communicated with the national road N-332 and the Mediterranean motorway AP-7. Close to major cities such as Murcia and Alicante.
</en><fr>Spacieux bungalow au rez-de-chaussée à Torre de la Horadada. Cette propriété moderne orientée au sud dispose de 4 chambres, 3 salles de bains, un salon-salle à manger spacieux avec cuisine ouverte et accès direct à la terrasse et au jardin de 120m2. Elle est située dans un complexe où vous pouvez profiter de la piscine commune et des zones de jardin. 

Torre de la Horadada est un quartier prestigieux de la Costa Blanca, très proche de Mil Palmeras, Campoamor, San Pedro del Pintar et Orihuela Costa. Les célèbres lagunes salées de San Pedro del Pinatar et le centre thermal marin Thalasia sont accessibles en seulement 10 minutes. Pilar De La Horadada bénéficie de plus de 2 500 heures d'ensoleillement par an et d'une température moyenne de 18ºC, ce qui en fait une zone privilégiée. Elle dispose d'un large éventail de services, d'espaces verts, de promenades et d'un port de plaisance. À seulement 5 minutes des centres commerciaux La Zenia Boulevard et Dos Mares. En plus de ces magnifiques conditions climatiques, il y a des plages de sable comme Playa Jesuitas, Playa del Puerto et Playa de las Higuericas. Bien desservi par la route nationale N-332 et l'autoroute méditerranéenne AP-7. Proche de grandes villes comme Murcia et Alicante.
</fr><ru>Просторное бунгало на первом этаже в Торре-де-ла-Орадада. Этот современный дом с южной стороны имеет 4 спальни, 3 ванные комнаты, просторную гостиную-столовую с кухней открытого плана и прямым выходом на террасу и в сад площадью 120 м2. Он расположен в комплексе, где вы можете наслаждаться общим бассейном и садом. 

Торре-де-ла-Орадада - престижный район на побережье Коста Бланка, очень близко к Миль Пальмерас, Кампоамор, Сан Педро дель Пинтар и Ориуэла Коста. До знаменитых соленых лагун Сан-Педро-дель-Пинатар и морского спа-центра Thalasia можно доехать всего за 10 минут. В Пилар-де-ла-Орадада более 2500 солнечных часов в году и средняя температура 18ºC, что делает его привилегированным районом. Здесь есть широкий спектр услуг, зеленые зоны, набережные и пристань для яхт. Всего в 5 минутах от торговых центров La Zenia Boulevard и Dos Mares. В дополнение к этим великолепным погодным условиям, здесь есть песчаные пляжи, такие как Плайя Хесуитас, Плайя дель Пуэрто и Плайя де лас Хигерикас. Хорошее сообщение с национальной дорогой N-332 и средиземноморской автомагистралью AP-7. Недалеко от крупных городов, таких как Мурсия и Аликанте.
</ru></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 65 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 0</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: </feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_1.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_2.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_3.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_4.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_5.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_6.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_7.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_8.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_9.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_10.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_11.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_12.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_13.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_14.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_15.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_16.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_17.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_18.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_19.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_20.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_21.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_22.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_23.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_24.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_25.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_26.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_27.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_28.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_29.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_30.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_31.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_32.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_33.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_34.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_35.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_36.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_37.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4142/4142_38.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>1092</id>
            <date>2025-01-09 09:41:00</date>
            <ref>4151</ref>
            <price>299900</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Apartment</type>
            <town>Orihuela Costa</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.937598000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.746758000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Villamartin</location_detail>
            <beds>3</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>1</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>106</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>C</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/apartments/tid4151</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/apartamentos/tid4151</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/appartements/tid4151</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/kvartiry/tid4151</ru>
            </url><virtual_tour_url>https://api.bennecke.com/p/embed/4151</virtual_tour_url><desc><es>Apartamento en 2ª planta en Villamartín, Orihuela Costa.

Os presentamos esta preciosa vivienda distribuida en tres habitaciones, una de ellas con baño en-suite. Un amplio salón-comedor con cocina americana y acceso directo a la terraza de 22m2 con vistas a las zonas comunes del residencial.

Se encuentra en residencial 'Gala' donde se puede disfrutar de piscina comunitaria, jacuzzi y zonas ajardinadas. Cuenta con su propia plaza de aparcamiento.

Villamartín es una prestigiosa zona dotada de todos los servicios y comodidades entre el golf y el mar. Muy cerca está La Zenia Boulevar, que es el centro comercial más grande de la provincia de Alicante. También en las cercanías esta el Campo de Golf de Villamartín, a 5 minutos de la playa, del Real Club de Golf Campoamor y del Campo de Golf Las Ramblas, rodeados de colegios, centros comerciales, restaurantes, farmacias, paradas de autobús que favorecen la estancia durante todo el año. Conecta fácilmente con la carretera nacional N-332 y la autovía del mediterráneo AP-7.</es><en>2nd floor apartment in Villamartin, Orihuela Costa.

We present this beautiful apartment distributed in three bedrooms, one of them with en-suite bathroom. A spacious living room with kitchenette and direct access to the terrace of 22m2 overlooking the common areas of the residential.

It is located in residential 'Gala' where you can enjoy a communal pool, jacuzzi and gardens. It has its own parking space.

Villamartin is a prestigious area with all the services and amenities between golf and the sea. Nearby is La Zenia Boulevard, which is the largest shopping center in the province of Alicante. Also nearby is the Villamartin Golf Course, 5 minutes from the beach, the Real Club de Golf Campoamor and Las Ramblas Golf Course, surrounded by schools, shopping centers, restaurants, pharmacies, bus stops that favor the stay throughout the year. It connects easily with the national road N-332 and the Mediterranean highway AP-7.
</en><fr>Appartement au 2ème étage à Villamartin, Orihuela Costa.

Nous présentons ce bel appartement distribué en trois chambres à coucher, l'une d'elles avec salle de bains en-suite. Un salon-salle à manger spacieux avec cuisine ouverte et accès direct à la terrasse de 22m2 avec vue sur les zones communes de la résidence.

Il est situé dans la résidence « Gala » où vous pouvez profiter de la piscine commune, du jacuzzi et des zones de jardin. Il dispose de sa propre place de parking.

Villamartin est une zone prestigieuse avec tous les services et commodités entre le golf et la mer. Le boulevard La Zenia, le plus grand centre commercial de la province d'Alicante, se trouve à proximité. Le terrain de golf de Villamartin, à 5 minutes de la plage, le Real Club de Golf Campoamor et le terrain de golf Las Ramblas se trouvent également à proximité, entourés d'écoles, de centres commerciaux, de restaurants, de pharmacies et d'arrêts de bus qui favorisent les séjours tout au long de l'année. Facilement relié à la route nationale N-332 et à l'autoroute méditerranéenne AP-7.</fr><ru>Апартаменты на 2 этаже в Вильямартине, Ориуэла-Коста.

Мы представляем эту прекрасную квартиру, состоящую из трех спален, одна из которых с ванной комнатой. Просторная гостиная-столовая с кухней открытого плана и прямым выходом на террасу 22м2 с видом на коммунальные зоны жилого комплекса.

Он расположен в жилом комплексе «Гала», где вы можете наслаждаться общим бассейном, джакузи и садовыми зонами. Имеется собственное парковочное место.

Вилламартин - престижный район со всеми услугами и удобствами между гольфом и морем. Рядом находится бульвар Ла Зения, который является крупнейшим торговым центром в провинции Аликанте. Также рядом находится поле для гольфа Villamartin, в 5 минутах от пляжа, Real Club de Golf Campoamor и Las Ramblas Golf Course, в окружении школ, торговых центров, ресторанов, аптек, автобусных остановок, которые благоприятствуют проживанию в течение всего года. Удобное сообщение с национальной дорогой N-332 и средиземноморской автомагистралью AP-7.
</ru></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 23 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 2</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Este</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: 2500</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_2.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_1.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_3.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_4.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_5.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_6.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_7.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_8.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_9.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_10.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_11.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_12.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_13.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_14.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_15.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_16.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_17.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_18.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_19.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_20.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_21.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_22.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_23.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_24.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_25.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_26.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_27.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_28.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_29.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_30.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_31.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_32.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_33.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_34.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_35.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4151/4151_36.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>1036</id>
            <date>2025-01-09 09:34:23</date>
            <ref>4161</ref>
            <price>895000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Villa</type>
            <town>Orihuela Costa</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.929735890000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.731772759000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>La Zenia</location_detail>
            <beds>5</beds><baths>4</baths><pool>1</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>296</built>
                <plot>410</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>E</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/villas/tid4161</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/villas/tid4161</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/villas/tid4161</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/villy/tid4161</ru>
            </url><virtual_tour_url>https://api.bennecke.com/p/embed/4161</virtual_tour_url><desc><es>Villa de lujo en La Zenia, Orihuela Costa.

Esta villa está situada en un residencial exclusivo y tiene su propia piscina privada y una parcela de 410m2. La vivienda cuenta con 250m2 construidos divididos en 4 plantas. En planta baja encontramos un amplio salón con cocina americana, 1 dormitorio, 1 baño y terraza con con salida a la piscina. En planta semi-sótano encontramos un salón con cocina americana, 2 dormitorios y 1 baño. Además esta planta cuenta con sauna y ducha. En planta primera encontramos 2 dormitorios, cada uno tiene uno baño en-suite y una amplia terraza. En la planta superior hay un amplio solarium de 46m2.

La Zenia está cerca de Cabo Roig, Campoamor y Playa Flamenca. Se trata de una zona turística ubicada cerca de todos los servicios del famoso centro comercial La Zenia Boulevard. A pocos minutos de la N -332 y la autopista del Mediterráneo AP-7 en dirección Alicante y Cartagena. También existen alrededor de los campos de golf de Villamartín, Las Ramblas, Campoamor y Las Colinas.</es><en>Luxury villa in La Zenia, Orihuela Costa.

This villa is situated in an exclusive residential area and has its own private pool and a plot of 410m2. The property has 250m2 built area divided into 4 floors. On the ground floor there is a spacious living room with open plan kitchen, 1 bedroom, 1 bathroom and terrace with access to the pool. On the semi-basement floor there is a living room with open plan kitchen, 2 bedrooms and 1 bathroom. This floor also has a sauna and shower. On the first floor there are 2 bedrooms, each with en-suite bathroom and a large terrace. On the top floor there is a large solarium of 46m2.

La Zenia is close to Cabo Roig, Campoamor and Playa Flamenca. It is a tourist area located close to all amenities of the famous La Zenia Boulevard shopping centre. A few minutes from the N-332 and the Mediterranean motorway AP-7 towards Alicante and Cartagena. There are also around the golf courses of Villamartin, Las Ramblas, Campoamor and Las Colinas.</en><fr>Villa de luxe à La Zenia, Orihuela Costa.

Cette villa est située dans un quartier résidentiel exclusif et dispose de sa propre piscine privée et d'un terrain de 410m2. La propriété a une surface construite de 250m2 divisée en 4 étages. Au rez-de-chaussée, il y a un salon spacieux avec cuisine ouverte, 1 chambre, 1 salle de bain et une terrasse avec accès à la piscine. Au sous-sol, il y a une salle de séjour avec cuisine ouverte, 2 chambres et 1 salle de bain. Cet étage dispose également d'un sauna et d'une douche. Au premier étage, il y a 2 chambres, chacune avec une salle de bain en-suite et une grande terrasse. Au dernier étage, il y a un grand solarium de 46m2.

La Zenia est proche de Cabo Roig, Campoamor et Playa Flamenca. C'est une zone touristique située à proximité de toutes les commodités du célèbre centre commercial La Zenia Boulevard. À quelques minutes de la N-332 et de l'autoroute méditerranéenne AP-7 en direction d'Alicante et de Carthagène. Les terrains de golf de Villamartin, Las Ramblas, Campoamor et Las Colinas se trouvent également à proximité.</fr><ru>Роскошная вилла в Ла-Зении, Ориуэла-Коста.

Вилла расположена в эксклюзивном жилом районе, имеет собственный бассейн и участок площадью 410 м2. Площадь дома составляет 250 м2 и разделена на 4 этажа. На первом этаже находится просторная гостиная с кухней открытого плана, 1 спальня, 1 ванная комната и терраса с выходом к бассейну. На полуподвальном этаже находится гостиная с кухней открытого плана, 2 спальни и 1 ванная комната. На этом этаже также есть сауна и душ. На втором этаже находятся 2 спальни, каждая с ванной комнатой и большой террасой. На верхнем этаже находится большой солярий площадью 46 м2.

Ла-Зения находится недалеко от Кабо-Роиг, Кампоамор и Плайя-Фламенка. Это туристический район, расположенный рядом со всеми удобствами знаменитого торгового центра La Zenia Boulevard. В нескольких минутах езды от шоссе N-332 и средиземноморской автомагистрали AP-7, ведущей в Аликанте и Картахену. Также рядом находятся поля для гольфа в Вилламартине, Лас-Рамбласе, Кампоаморе и Лас-Колинасе.</ru></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 0 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 0</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur/Este</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium (m2): 46</feature>
                <feature>Distance sea: 500</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_1.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_2.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_19.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_4.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_16.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_6.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_7.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_15.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_8.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_17.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_9.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_10.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_11.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_12.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_13.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_14.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_18.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_21.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_22.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_23.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_24.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_28.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_25.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_31.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_32.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_33.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_34.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_46.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_26.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_27.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_20.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_30.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_29.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_59.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_57.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_5.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_54.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_55.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_36.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="40">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_48.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="41">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_39.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="42">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_42.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="43">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_40.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="44">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_41.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="45">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_43.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="46">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_44.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="47">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_45.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="48">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_47.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="49">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_49.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="50">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4161/4161_50.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3010</id>
            <date>2025-05-22 12:01:01</date>
            <ref>4181</ref>
            <price>749900</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Villa</type>
            <town>Orihuela Costa</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.945543000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.715504199999</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Punta Prima</location_detail>
            <beds>4</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>168</built>
                <plot>540</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>G</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/villas/tid4181</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/villas/tid4181</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/villas/tid4181</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/villy/tid4181</ru>
            </url><virtual_tour_url>https://api.bennecke.com/p/embed/4181</virtual_tour_url><desc><es>Presentamos esta encantadora villa situada en una de las zonas más privilegiadas de la Costa Blanca: Punta Prima, a tan solo unos pasos del mar.

La vivienda cuenta con una superficie construida de 168 m², ubicada sobre una amplia parcela de 540 m², ofreciendo privacidad, comodidad y espacio para disfrutar al aire libre.

La villa se distribuye en 4 amplios dormitorios, 2 baños completos, un luminoso salón-comedor con acceso directo al exterior y una moderna cocina americana totalmente equipada.
En el exterior, la propiedad ofrece una magnífica piscina privada, zona de barbacoa, terrazas soleadas y un jardín mediterráneo – ideal para disfrutar del clima durante todo el año.

Punta Prima es una zona costera consolidada, famosa por su acceso directo al mar, playas de arena fina, calas naturales y un entorno tranquilo. A poca distancia se encuentran todos los servicios necesarios: restaurantes, supermercados, farmacias, centros comerciales como La Zenia Boulevard, y una excelente conexión con las principales vías de comunicación. A tan solo 10 minutos en coche del centro de Torrevieja y rodeada de campos de golf, centros deportivos y zonas verdes.</es><fr>Nous vous présentons cette charmante villa située dans l’un des quartiers les plus privilégiés de la Costa Blanca : Punta Prima, à seulement quelques pas de la mer.

La propriété offre une surface construite de 168 m², sur un terrain spacieux de 540 m², offrant intimité, confort et de grands espaces extérieurs pour en profiter pleinement.

La villa se compose de 4 grandes chambres, 2 salles de bains complètes, d’un salon-salle à manger lumineux avec accès direct à l’extérieur, ainsi qu’une cuisine américaine moderne entièrement équipée.
À l’extérieur, vous trouverez une piscine privée, un espace barbecue, des terrasses ensoleillées et un jardin méditerranéen – parfait pour profiter du climat tout au long de l’année.

Punta Prima est une zone côtière consolidée, réputée pour son accès direct à la mer, ses plages de sable fin, ses criques naturelles et son environnement paisible. Tous les services essentiels sont à proximité : restaurants, supermarchés, pharmacies, centres commerciaux comme La Zenia Boulevard, et d'excellentes connexions routières. À seulement 10 minutes en voiture du centre de Torrevieja, entourée de terrains de golf, d’installations sportives et d’espaces verts.</fr><ru>Представляем вашему вниманию очаровательную виллу, расположенную в одном из самых привилегированных районов Коста Бланки – Пунта Прима, всего в нескольких шагах от моря.

Жилая площадь виллы составляет 168 м², а участок – 540 м², что обеспечивает уединение, комфорт и достаточно пространства для отдыха на свежем воздухе.

Вилла включает в себя 4 просторные спальни, 2 ванные комнаты, светлую гостиную-столовую с выходом на террасу, а также современную кухню американского типа, полностью оборудованную.
На участке вы найдёте частный бассейн, зону барбекю, солнечные террасы и средиземноморский сад – идеальное место для отдыха круглый год.

Пунта Прима – это развитый прибрежный район с прямым выходом к морю, песчаными пляжами, природными бухтами и спокойной атмосферой. Поблизости находятся все необходимые удобства: рестораны, супермаркеты, аптеки, торговые центры, такие как La Zenia Boulevard, а также отличное транспортное сообщение. Всего в 10 минутах езды от центра Торревьехи, в окружении полей для гольфа, спортивных комплексов и зелёных зон.</ru><en>We present this charming villa located in one of the most privileged areas of the Costa Blanca: Punta Prima, just a few steps from the sea.

The property has a built area of 168 m², set on a spacious 540 m² plot, offering privacy, comfort, and ample outdoor space to enjoy.

The villa features 4 spacious bedrooms, 2 full bathrooms, a bright living-dining room with direct access to the exterior, and a modern fully equipped open-plan kitchen.
Outside, the property boasts a private pool, barbecue area, sunny terraces, and a Mediterranean garden – ideal for enjoying the climate all year round.

Punta Prima is a well-established coastal area, known for its direct access to the sea, fine sandy beaches, natural coves, and peaceful environment. All essential services are nearby: restaurants, supermarkets, pharmacies, shopping centres such as La Zenia Boulevard, and excellent road connections. Just 10 minutes by car from the centre of Torrevieja, and surrounded by golf courses, sports facilities, and green areas.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 0 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: </feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur/Oeste</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: 500</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4adaf36_010013.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4a23e10_010001.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4a269bc_010002.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4a42cb1_010003.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4a45125_010004.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4a61ad3_010005.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4a650be_010006.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4a7ff69_010007.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4a83641_010008.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4a9e08a_010009.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4aa11cd_010010.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4aba998_010011.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4ac0a05_010012.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4add5f9_010014.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4b074fe_010015.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4b0dd20_010016.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4b267b7_010017.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4b27a1c_010018.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4b46a7e_010019.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4b47fea_010020.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4b66b2e_010021.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4b69418_010022.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4b883ce_010023.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4b89a79_010024.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4ba9abe_010025.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4bab3cf_010026.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4bc59ff_interior0001.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4bc78fe_interior0002.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4be13c9_interior0003.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4be350c_interior0004.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c088af_interior0005.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c0c979_interior0006.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c23470_interior0007.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c270b0_interior0008.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c3f2fd_interior0009.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c40bb0_interior0010.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c5a3cd_interior0011.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c5c854_interior0012.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c72526_interior0013.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="40">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c773c0_interior0014.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="41">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c8b4a6_interior0015.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="42">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4c8e921_interior0016.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="43">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4ca4190_interior0017.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="44">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4ca6940_interior0018.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="45">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4cbb794_interior0019.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="46">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4cbf14d_interior0020.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="47">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4cd284b_interior0021.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="48">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4cd6d4e_interior0022.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="49">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4ceb511_interior0023.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="50">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4181/68356c4cefe31_interior0024.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3028</id>
            <date>2025-05-26 13:01:09</date>
            <ref>4182RV</ref>
            <price>210000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Apartment</type>
            <town>Torrevieja</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.951364100000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.718281000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Los Altos</location_detail>
            <beds>2</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>65</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>D</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/apartments/tid4182RV</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/apartamentos/tid4182RV</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/appartements/tid4182RV</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/kvartiry/tid4182RV</ru>
            </url><virtual_tour_url>https://api.bennecke.com/p/embed/4182RV</virtual_tour_url><desc><es>Presentamos este magnífico ático de esquina situado en una urbanización privada y consolidada, que ofrece una piscina comunitaria y zonas comunes de alta calidad, en la prestigiosa zona de Punta Marina, Punta Prima.

La propiedad se encuentra en un estado impecable y destaca por su elegante estilo rústico, que aporta un ambiente cálido y acogedor. Su orientación oeste garantiza una excelente iluminación natural durante la tarde, creando espacios luminosos y agradables.

Este ático dispone de un amplio solárium privado, ideal para disfrutar del sol y de las vistas despejadas a la calle en un entorno tranquilo y privilegiado.

Una oportunidad única para quienes buscan una residencia principal, una segunda vivienda o una inversión con alto potencial en una de las zonas más demandadas.
Si desean concertar una visita o recibir más información, no duden en ponerse en contacto con nosotros.

</es><fr>Penthouse d’angle exclusif au style rustique dans une résidence privée avec piscine – Punta Marina, Punta Prima

Nous vous présentons ce magnifique penthouse d’angle situé dans une résidence privée bien établie, offrant une piscine commune et des espaces communs de haute qualité, dans le prestigieux secteur de Punta Marina à Punta Prima.

Le bien est en excellent état et se distingue par son élégant style rustique, créant une ambiance chaleureuse et accueillante. Son orientation ouest garantit une excellente luminosité naturelle l’après-midi, offrant des espaces de vie lumineux et agréables.

Ce penthouse dispose d’un grand solarium privé, idéal pour profiter du soleil et des vues dégagées sur la rue dans un cadre paisible et privilégié.

Une opportunité unique pour ceux qui recherchent une résidence principale, une maison de vacances ou un investissement à fort potentiel dans l’une des zones les plus prisées.

Si vous souhaitez organiser une visite ou obtenir plus d’informations, n’hésitez pas à nous contacter.

</fr><ru>Представляем вашему вниманию великолепный угловой пентхаус, расположенный в престижном закрытом жилом комплексе с общим бассейном и высококачественными удобствами, в районе Пунта Марина, Пунта Прима.

Квартира находится в безупречном состоянии и выделяется элегантным рустикальным стилем, создающим тёплую и уютную атмосферу. Ориентация на запад обеспечивает прекрасное естественное освещение во второй половине дня, что делает жилые помещения светлыми и комфортными.

Пентхаус располагает просторным частным солярием, идеальным для принятия солнечных ванн и наслаждения открытым видом на улицу в тихой и привилегированной обстановке.

Это уникальная возможность для тех, кто ищет основное жильё, загородный дом для отдыха или выгодную инвестицию в одном из самых востребованных районов.

Если вы хотите назначить просмотр или получить дополнительную информацию, пожалуйста, свяжитесь с нами без колебаний.

</ru><en>We are pleased to present this outstanding corner penthouse located in a well-established private residential complex featuring a communal swimming pool and high-quality shared amenities, situated in the prestigious Punta Marina area of Punta Prima.

The property is in impeccable condition and stands out for its elegant rustic style, creating a warm and inviting atmosphere. Its west-facing orientation ensures excellent natural light during the afternoon, resulting in bright and pleasant living spaces.

This penthouse includes a spacious private solarium, ideal for enjoying the sun and unobstructed views of the street in a peaceful and privileged setting.

An exceptional opportunity for those seeking a primary residence, a vacation home, or a high-potential investment in one of the most sought-after locations.

If you would like to schedule a viewing or request further information, please do not hesitate to contact us.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 0 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 1</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Oeste</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium (m2): 15</feature>
                <feature>Distance sea: 1000</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2b9877b_int0002.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2b84333_int0001.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2bab613_int0003.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2bbb67f_int0004.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2bcae9b_int0005.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b293a234_010004.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2918f94_010003.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b294e1d9_010005.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2be21eb_int0006.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2bf2362_int0007.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2c1259d_int0008.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2c468fd_int0009.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2c57f35_int0010.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2c6e282_int0011.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2c80735_int0012.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2967e60_010006.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2979c91_010007.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b29a1085_010009.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b298d057_010008.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2cc63ff_int0015.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2cde6bc_int0016.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2ced25f_int0017.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2d1385e_int0018.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2d2b755_int0019.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2d3d63e_int0020.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2c8e414_int0013.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2ca9a97_int0014.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2d549f8_int0021.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2b70e06_DJI_0752.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2b4c919_DJI_0751.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b28efeb2_010001.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b28eccfc_010002.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b29e4101_010011.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2a0afe4_DJI_0728.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4182RV/683d7b2b2b93b_DJI_0731.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3174</id>
            <date>2025-07-03 12:28:10</date>
            <ref>4186</ref>
            <price>656000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Villa</type>
            <town>Torrevieja</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.947289500000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.706057300000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Rocio del Mar</location_detail>
            <beds>4</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>141</built>
                <plot>442</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>D</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/villas/tid4186</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/villas/tid4186</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/villas/tid4186</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/villy/tid4186</ru>
            </url><virtual_tour_url>https://api.bennecke.com/p/embed/4186</virtual_tour_url><desc><es>Te presentamos esta magnífica vivienda unifamiliar ubicada en una de las zonas más codiciadas de la costa: Rocío del Mar, a tan solo 200 metros de la playa. Se trata de un chalet semi-adosado distribuido en dos plantas, con una superficie construida de 141 m² sobre una parcela privada de 442 m².
La propiedad ofrece cuatro dormitorios espaciosos y dos baños completos, con una distribución interior cómoda y funcional que garantiza una excelente luminosidad y ventilación natural en todas las estancias. Desde la planta superior se disfrutan agradables vistas al mar, añadiendo un valor especial a esta vivienda.
El exterior destaca por su estupenda piscina privada, perfecta para relajarse y disfrutar del clima mediterráneo durante todo el año, además de amplias zonas de terraza y un cuidado jardín que invitan a compartir momentos inolvidables en familia o con amigos.
La villa se entrega completamente amueblada y equipada con electrodomésticos, aire acondicionado, sistema de alarma y todas las comodidades necesarias para instalarse y disfrutar desde el primer día.
Una opción ideal tanto como residencia habitual como para uso vacacional, situada en un entorno tranquilo y residencial, pero con todos los servicios esenciales a pocos minutos.</es><fr>Nous vous présentons cette magnifique maison individuelle située dans l’un des quartiers les plus prisés de la côte : Rocío del Mar, à seulement 200 mètres de la plage. Il s’agit d’une villa jumelée répartie sur deux étages, avec une surface construite de 141 m² sur un terrain privé de 442 m².
La propriété offre quatre chambres spacieuses et deux salles de bains complètes, avec une distribution intérieure confortable et fonctionnelle garantissant une excellente luminosité et une ventilation naturelle dans toutes les pièces. Depuis l’étage supérieur, on profite d’une agréable vue sur la mer, ajoutant une valeur supplémentaire à cette maison.
À l’extérieur, on apprécie particulièrement sa belle piscine privée, parfaite pour se détendre et profiter du climat méditerranéen tout au long de l’année, ainsi que de vastes terrasses et un jardin soigné, idéals pour partager des moments inoubliables en famille ou entre amis.
La villa est vendue entièrement meublée et équipée avec électroménagers, climatisation, système d’alarme et tout le confort nécessaire pour s’installer et en profiter immédiatement.
Une option idéale tant comme résidence principale que comme maison de vacances, située dans un environnement résidentiel calme mais à proximité de tous les services essentiels.</fr><ru>Предлагаем вашему вниманию великолепный дом, расположенный в одном из самых востребованных районов побережья — Росио-дель-Мар, всего в 200 метрах от пляжа. Это двухэтажный смежный коттедж с общей застроенной площадью 141 м² на частном участке площадью 442 м².
В доме четыре просторные спальни и два полностью оборудованных санузла. Удобная и функциональная планировка обеспечивает отличное естественное освещение и вентиляцию во всех помещениях. С верхнего этажа открывается приятный вид на море, что придаёт дому особую ценность.
Во дворе расположен великолепный частный бассейн, идеально подходящий для отдыха и наслаждения средиземноморским климатом круглый год, а также просторные террасы и ухоженный сад для приятного времяпрепровождения с семьёй и друзьями.
Вилла продаётся полностью меблированной и оснащённой всей необходимой бытовой техникой, системой кондиционирования воздуха, сигнализацией и всеми удобствами для комфортного проживания с первого дня.
Идеальный вариант как для постоянного проживания, так и для отдыха — в тихом жилом районе с полной инфраструктурой поблизости.</ru><en>We present this magnificent detached house located in one of the most sought-after areas of the coast: Rocío del Mar, just 200 metres from the beach. This semi-detached villa is distributed over two floors, with a built area of 141 m² on a private plot of 442 m².
The property offers four spacious bedrooms and two full bathrooms, with a comfortable and functional layout that ensures excellent natural light and ventilation in every room. From the upper floor you can enjoy pleasant sea views, adding special value to this home.
Outside, the highlight is its beautiful private pool, perfect for relaxing and enjoying the Mediterranean climate all year round, along with large terrace areas and a well-kept garden ideal for unforgettable moments with family and friends.
The villa is sold fully furnished and equipped with all appliances, air conditioning, an alarm system, and all the necessary comforts to move in and enjoy immediately.
An ideal option both as a permanent residence and as a holiday home, located in a quiet residential area yet very close to all essential services.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 0 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: </feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Este</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium (m2): 30</feature>
                <feature>Distance sea: 200</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff7e5ab_T73A0410.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe1e855_010001.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe1fad3_010003.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe3b129_010004.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe4d500_010008.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe3ef64_010005.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe4f488_010009.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe5fb58_010014.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe6918f_010011.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe798f0_010015.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe8355c_010016.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe934d9_010019.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fe94f72_010018.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fea40e6_010020.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fea4b2c_010021.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08febf2ad_010025.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08febfef1_010022.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fed0b25_010027.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fedb6e1_010026.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fee15ee_010029.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08fef3721_010032.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff0357b_010031.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff14dc6_010034.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff18dc4_010033.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff26ecd_010036.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff29287_010037.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff3893b_010040.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff3ae32_010041.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff53883_010042.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff555d5_DJI_0049 copy.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff6545b_T73A0404.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff6df13_DJI_0052 copy.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff7630d_T73A0406.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff86b2e_T73A0413.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff8f134_T73A0415.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ff9819c_T73A0417.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ffa971c_T73A0423.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ffb23b7_T73A0426.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4186/687e08ffc3ce6_T73A0429.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3217</id>
            <date>2025-07-28 16:46:09</date>
            <ref>4187RV</ref>
            <price>245000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Apartment</type>
            <town>Orihuela Costa</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.936654100000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.749282999999</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Villamartin</location_detail>
            <beds>2</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>93</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>C</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/apartments/tid4187RV</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/apartamentos/tid4187RV</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/appartements/tid4187RV</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/kvartiry/tid4187RV</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Este exclusivo apartamento se encuentra en Green Hills, una de las urbanizaciones más modernas y completas de Villamartín, en Orihuela Costa. Con una superficie construida de 93 m², la vivienda se distribuye en dos dormitorios y dos baños, ofreciendo espacios amplios, luminosos y con un diseño contemporáneo. Además, cuenta con una amplia terraza, ideal para disfrutar del clima mediterráneo.

La vivienda se entrega sin amueblar, brindando la oportunidad de personalizar cada espacio al gusto del nuevo propietario.

Ubicado dentro del residencial Green Hills, este complejo destaca por su excelente oferta de servicios: piscina comunitaria al aire libre, piscina climatizada, sauna y un gimnasio completamente equipado, lo que lo convierte en un entorno perfecto para el bienestar y el relax durante todo el año.

Situado a tan solo 3 km del mar, este ático permite un acceso rápido a las hermosas playas de Orihuela Costa. La zona de Villamartín es reconocida por sus prestigiosos campos de golf y su completa oferta de servicios, incluyendo supermercados, restaurantes y centros comerciales. Su excelente infraestructura y conexiones de transporte facilitan el acceso a otras zonas de interés de la Costa Blanca, convirtiendo esta propiedad en una opción ideal tanto como residencia permanente como para inversión vacacional.</es><fr>Cet appartement exclusif est situé dans la résidence Green Hills, l’une des plus modernes et complètes de Villamartín, à Orihuela Costa. Avec une surface construite de 93 m², le bien comprend deux chambres et deux salles de bains, offrant des espaces lumineux et spacieux au design contemporain. Il dispose également d’une grande terrasse, idéale pour profiter du climat méditerranéen.

Le logement est vendu non meublé, laissant la possibilité de l’aménager à votre goût.

La résidence Green Hills propose de nombreuses commodités : piscine extérieure, piscine intérieure chauffée, sauna et salle de sport entièrement équipée, créant un environnement parfait pour le confort et la détente toute l’année.

Situé à seulement 3 km de la mer, ce penthouse offre un accès rapide aux magnifiques plages d’Orihuela Costa. Le quartier de Villamartín est réputé pour ses prestigieux parcours de golf, ainsi que pour sa large gamme de services : supermarchés, restaurants et centres commerciaux. Grâce à une excellente infrastructure et des connexions de transport efficaces, cette propriété est idéale en tant que résidence principale ou investissement locatif.</fr><ru>Эти эксклюзивные апартаменты расположены в жилом комплексе Грин-Хиллс, одном из самых современных и хорошо оборудованных районов Вильямартина в Ориуэла Коста. Общая площадь составляет 93 м², в квартире — две спальни и две ванные комнаты, просторная планировка и современный дизайн. Также имеется большая терраса, идеально подходящая для отдыха на свежем воздухе.

Квартира продаётся без мебели, что даёт возможность оформить интерьер по своему вкусу.

Жилой комплекс Грин-Хиллс предлагает отличную инфраструктуру: открытый бассейн, подогреваемый крытый бассейн, сауна, а также полностью оборудованный тренажёрный зал — идеальное место для жизни и отдыха круглый год.

Пентхаус расположен всего в 3 км от моря, что обеспечивает быстрый доступ к прекрасным пляжам Ориуэла Коста. Район Вильямартин известен своими престижными гольф-полями и широким выбором услуг — супермаркеты, рестораны и торговые центры. Благодаря отличной транспортной доступности, эта недвижимость идеально подойдёт как для постоянного проживания, так и для инвестиций в аренду.</ru><en>This exclusive apartment is located in Green Hills, one of the most modern and well-equipped residential complexes in Villamartín, Orihuela Costa. With a built area of 93 m², the property features two bedrooms and two bathrooms, offering spacious and bright interiors with a contemporary design. It also boasts a large terrace, perfect for enjoying the Mediterranean climate.

The apartment is sold unfurnished, allowing the new owner to customize it to their own taste.

Green Hills offers excellent communal facilities, including an outdoor pool, heated indoor pool, sauna, and a fully equipped gym, making it an ideal setting for year-round comfort and relaxation.

Located just 3 km from the sea, the penthouse provides quick access to the beautiful beaches of Orihuela Costa. The Villamartín area is renowned for its prestigious golf courses and a wide range of services, such as supermarkets, restaurants, and shopping centers. Thanks to its excellent infrastructure and transport connections, this property is ideal as a permanent residence or a holiday investment.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 13 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 1</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Norte</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: 3000</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f2952dc_4153_6.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f27b5de_4153_3.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a3744afe_IMG_0254.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a3735f47_IMG_0252.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a373f2d3_IMG_0253.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a36e0668_IMG_0235.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a36dc423_IMG_0236.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a36f1597_IMG_0237.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a374e13e_IMG_0255.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a370ea9f_IMG_0240.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a371857c_IMG_0241.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a3718cfe_IMG_0244.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a372190c_IMG_0245.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a37276fd_IMG_0246.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a36f1e0a_IMG_0238.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/68879a370f5e3_IMG_0239.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f28f92e_4153_4.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f2a6892_4153_8.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f2aa6a6_4153_29.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f2bc78e_4153_30.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f2cd913_4153_31.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f2df565_4153_32.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f2f0b3d_4153_33.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f30f28a_4153_34.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f31242c_4153_35.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f32aae2_4153_38.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f2792e5_4153_2.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f321e4c_4153_39.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f332e7c_4153_40.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f346e27_4153_41.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f34432e_4153_43.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f35f26a_4153_44.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f357a09_4153_45.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4187RV/6887a1f3683c7_4153_46.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3281</id>
            <date>2025-08-27 11:09:34</date>
            <ref>4190</ref>
            <price>339000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Townhouse</type>
            <town>Torrevieja</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.961896000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.719519000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Los Balcones</location_detail>
            <beds>3</beds><baths>3</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>113</built>
                <plot>22</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>C</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/townhouses/tid4190</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/adosados/tid4190</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/maisons-de-villes/tid4190</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/tounkhausy/tid4190</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Este adosado dúplex de tres dormitorios y tres baños se encuentra en la exclusiva zona residencial de Los Balcones, en Torrevieja. La vivienda destaca por su diseño moderno, la luminosidad en cada estancia y sus amplias terrazas que permiten disfrutar del estilo de vida mediterráneo durante todo el año.

En la planta baja, la vivienda dispone de un jardín privado de 22 m² con espacio para comedor exterior. El interior cuenta con un salón de concepto abierto, decorado con un elegante revestimiento en la pared principal, conectado a una cocina moderna totalmente equipada con electrodomésticos y barra americana. En esta planta también se sitúa un dormitorio con armario empotrado, actualmente adaptado como zona de trabajo, además de un baño completo con ducha.

En la planta superior se encuentran dos dormitorios, ambos con armarios empotrados, siendo el principal muy luminoso y con acceso directo a una terraza privada con vistas a la urbanización y a la piscina. En esta planta se ubican también dos baños completos con acabados de alta calidad.

La vivienda cuenta con un amplio solárium privado con vistas despejadas a la laguna de Torrevieja, equipado con zona chill-out, pérgola, barbacoa y tumbonas, perfecto para disfrutar de reuniones al aire libre o de la tranquilidad del entorno.

El residencial ofrece amplias zonas comunes con piscina comunitaria de gran tamaño rodeada de palmeras y zonas verdes, lo que genera un ambiente ideal tanto para familias como para quienes buscan un entorno relajado.

La urbanización de Los Balcones es una de las más consolidadas de Torrevieja, con todos los servicios al alcance: supermercados, colegios, farmacias, zonas deportivas y el Hospital Universitario de Torrevieja. Las playas de Punta Prima y Torrevieja se encuentran a menos de 4 km, lo que convierte esta propiedad en una excelente opción tanto como residencia permanente como para inversión vacacional.</es><fr>Cette maison mitoyenne en duplex de trois chambres et trois salles de bain se situe dans le quartier résidentiel exclusif de Los Balcones à Torrevieja. Elle se distingue par son design moderne, sa luminosité dans chaque pièce et ses grandes terrasses qui permettent de profiter du style de vie méditerranéen tout au long de l’année.
Au rez-de-chaussée, la maison dispose d’un jardin privé de 22 m² avec espace repas extérieur. L’intérieur comprend un salon décloisonné avec un élégant mur décoratif, relié à une cuisine moderne entièrement équipée avec électroménagers et bar américain. Ce niveau comprend également une chambre avec placard intégré, actuellement aménagée en bureau, ainsi qu’une salle de bain complète avec douche.
À l’étage, se trouvent deux chambres supplémentaires, toutes deux avec placards intégrés. La chambre principale, très lumineuse, bénéficie d’un accès direct à une terrasse privée avec vue sur la résidence et la piscine. Cet étage dispose également de deux autres salles de bain modernes et entièrement équipées.
La maison dispose en outre d’un grand solarium privé avec vue dégagée sur la lagune de Torrevieja, équipé d’un espace chill-out, d’une pergola, d’un barbecue et de transats — parfait pour les réunions en plein air ou pour profiter du calme environnant.
La résidence offre de vastes espaces communs avec une grande piscine entourée de palmiers et d’espaces verts, créant un cadre idéal pour les familles ou pour ceux qui recherchent un mode de vie paisible.
Los Balcones est l’un des quartiers résidentiels les plus établis de Torrevieja, avec tous les services à proximité : supermarchés, écoles, pharmacies, installations sportives et l’Hôpital Universitaire de Torrevieja. Les plages de Punta Prima et de Torrevieja se trouvent à moins de 4 km, ce qui fait de cette propriété un excellent choix, aussi bien comme résidence principale que comme investissement pour les vacances.</fr><ru>Этот двухуровневый таунхаус с тремя спальнями и тремя ванными комнатами расположен в престижном жилом районе Лос-Балконес в Торревьехе. Дом выделяется современным дизайном, светлыми интерьерами и просторными террасами, позволяющими наслаждаться средиземноморским образом жизни круглый год.
На первом этаже находится частный сад площадью 22 м² с местом для обедов на свежем воздухе. Внутри — гостиная открытой планировки с элегантной декоративной стеной, соединённая с современной кухней, полностью оборудованной техникой и барной стойкой. На этом уровне также расположена спальня с встроенным шкафом (сейчас используется как кабинет) и ванная комната с душем.
На втором этаже находятся ещё две спальни с встроенными шкафами. Главная спальня очень светлая и имеет выход на частную террасу с видом на урбанизацию и бассейн. Здесь же расположены ещё две ванные комнаты с современными отделочными материалами.
На верхнем уровне — просторный частный солярий с панорамным видом на лагуну Торревьехи, оборудованный зоной отдыха, перголой, барбекю и шезлонгами — идеальное место для встреч на свежем воздухе или спокойного отдыха.
Жилой комплекс располагает просторными общими зонами с большим бассейном, окружённым пальмами и зелёными насаждениями, что создаёт атмосферу уюта и отдыха как для семей, так и для тех, кто ищет спокойную жизнь у моря.
Лос-Балконес — один из самых обустроенных районов Торревьехи, где есть всё необходимое: супермаркеты, школы, аптеки, спортивные площадки и Университетская больница Торревьехи. Пляжи Пунта-Прима и Торревьехи находятся менее чем в 4 км, что делает этот дом отличным выбором как для постоянного проживания, так и для инвестиций в аренду или отдых.</ru><en>This three-bedroom, three-bathroom duplex townhouse is located in the exclusive residential area of Los Balcones in Torrevieja. The property stands out for its modern design, bright interiors and spacious terraces that allow you to enjoy the Mediterranean lifestyle all year round.
On the ground floor, the house features a private 22 m² garden with space for outdoor dining. Inside, there is an open-plan living room with an elegant feature wall, connected to a fully equipped modern kitchen with appliances and breakfast bar. This level also includes a bedroom with fitted wardrobes, currently adapted as a study, and a complete bathroom with shower.
Upstairs, there are two further bedrooms, both with fitted wardrobes. The master bedroom is particularly bright and has direct access to a private terrace with views of the residential area and the swimming pool. This floor also offers two additional bathrooms with modern finishes.
The property also benefits from a large private solarium with open views of the Torrevieja lagoon, equipped with a chill-out area, pergola, barbecue and sun loungers — perfect for outdoor gatherings or simply relaxing in a peaceful setting.
The residential complex offers large communal areas with a swimming pool surrounded by palm trees and green spaces, creating an ideal environment for families or those seeking a relaxed lifestyle.
Los Balcones is one of the most established residential areas of Torrevieja, with all services nearby: supermarkets, schools, pharmacies, sports facilities and Torrevieja University Hospital. The beaches of Punta Prima and Torrevieja are less than 4 km away, making this property an excellent choice both as a permanent residence or a holiday investment.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 15 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: </feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Oeste</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium (m2): 20</feature>
                <feature>Distance sea: 2500</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9d60506_IMG_0776.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9d42fdd_IMG_0773.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c5cbe5_IMG_0708.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c5bdfa_IMG_0706.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c74dee_IMG_0709.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c7e843_IMG_0710.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c04696_IMG_0695.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c49da5_IMG_0701.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c0517c_IMG_0696.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c1fda9_IMG_0697.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c178e4_IMG_0698.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c2cec9_IMG_0699.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c3f61f_IMG_0700.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9cb4468_IMG_0737.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9ceea3c_IMG_0758.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9d0bf62_IMG_0759.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9d0cfef_IMG_0760.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9d45e2a_IMG_0764.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9d1ecf6_IMG_0762.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9d307c1_IMG_0763.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9d28ca1_IMG_0761.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c92583_IMG_0718.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c8a024_IMG_0717.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9c9c25b_IMG_0719.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9bd5266_IMG_0681.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9bcc4a4_IMG_0682.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9cedf39_IMG_0755.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9cd2129_IMG_0754.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9cbfee0_IMG_0750.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4190/68b6ca9cd0d0a_IMG_0752.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3287</id>
            <date>2025-09-01 17:29:29</date>
            <ref>4192RV</ref>
            <price>225000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Apartment</type>
            <town>Orihuela Costa</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.926868000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.728402000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>La Zenia</location_detail>
            <beds>2</beds><baths>1</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>64</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>D</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/apartments/tid4192RV</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/apartamentos/tid4192RV</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/appartements/tid4192RV</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/kvartiry/tid4192RV</ru>
            </url><desc><es>En la urbanización Zeniasol, a pocos pasos de la playa de La Zenia y del centro comercial Zenia Boulevard, se encuentra este luminoso bungalow de planta alta en esquina, en excelente estado de conservación.

La vivienda ofrece un salón-comedor acogedor con cocina americana totalmente equipada, dos dormitorios dobles con armarios empotrados y un baño completo renovado con ducha. Su orientación y ventanales aportan gran luminosidad a todas las estancias, creando un ambiente cálido y confortable.

Uno de sus grandes atractivos es el solárium privado de aproximadamente 40 m², perfecto para disfrutar del sol durante todo el año. Dispone de barbacoa de obra y espacio suficiente para habilitar zonas de relax, comedor al aire libre o incluso un área chill out con vistas despejadas.

El complejo cuenta con piscina comunitaria rodeada de zonas ajardinadas y la propiedad dispone además de plaza exterior de aparcamiento.

Su localización es privilegiada: en un entorno tranquilo pero con todos los servicios al alcance de la mano, como supermercados, restaurantes, colegios, transporte público y zonas de ocio. La playa y el centro comercial Zenia Boulevard se encuentran a escasa distancia andando.

Una vivienda ideal tanto como residencia vacacional como inversión de alquiler, en una de las zonas más demandadas de Orihuela Costa.</es><fr>Situé dans la résidence Zeniasol, à quelques pas de la plage de La Zenia et du centre commercial Zenia Boulevard, ce lumineux bungalow en angle à l’étage supérieur se présente en excellent état.

Il offre un salon-salle à manger confortable avec cuisine américaine entièrement équipée, deux chambres doubles avec placards intégrés ainsi qu’une salle de bain rénovée avec douche. De grandes fenêtres apportent une belle luminosité dans toutes les pièces, créant une atmosphère chaleureuse et agréable.

L’un de ses principaux atouts est le solarium privé d’environ 40 m², idéal pour profiter du soleil toute l’année. Il dispose d’un barbecue en dur et offre suffisamment d’espace pour aménager une zone de détente, une salle à manger extérieure ou un espace chill-out avec vue dégagée.

La résidence dispose d’une piscine communautaire entourée de jardins, et le logement comprend également une place de stationnement extérieure.

Son emplacement est privilégié : dans un cadre calme mais à proximité immédiate de tous les services comme supermarchés, restaurants, écoles, transports publics et zones de loisirs. La plage et Zenia Boulevard sont accessibles à pied en quelques minutes.

Un bien idéal, aussi bien comme résidence de vacances que comme investissement locatif, dans l’une des zones les plus recherchées de la Costa d’Orihuela.</fr><ru>В урбанизации Zeniasol, всего в нескольких минутах ходьбы от пляжа Ла-Зения и торгового центра Zenia Boulevard, предлагается светлое угловое бунгало на верхнем этаже в отличном состоянии.

Жильё включает уютную гостиную-столовую с полностью оборудованной кухней открытого типа, две спальни с встроенными шкафами и обновлённую ванную комнату с душем. Большие окна наполняют дом естественным светом и создают тёплую атмосферу.

Особое преимущество – частный солярий площадью около 40 м², где можно наслаждаться солнцем круглый год. Здесь есть встроенный барбекю и достаточно места для организации зоны отдыха, обеденной зоны на свежем воздухе или лаундж-зоны с открытым видом.

В комплексе предусмотрен общий бассейн, окружённый зелёными насаждениями, а также жильцам предоставляется собственное парковочное место.

Расположение очень удобное: тихий жилой район, но рядом все необходимые услуги – супермаркеты, рестораны, школы, общественный транспорт и зоны отдыха. До пляжа и Zenia Boulevard можно дойти пешком за несколько минут.

Отличный вариант как для отдыха, так и для аренды – в одном из самых востребованных районов Ла-Зении, Ориуэла-Коста.</ru><en>Located in the Zeniasol residential complex, just a short walk from La Zenia beach and the Zenia Boulevard shopping centre, this bright top-floor corner bungalow is in excellent condition.

The property features a cosy living-dining room with a fully equipped open-plan kitchen, two double bedrooms with fitted wardrobes and a renovated bathroom with shower. Large windows provide plenty of natural light throughout, creating a warm and comfortable atmosphere.

One of the highlights is the private solarium of approximately 40 m², perfect to enjoy the sun all year round. It includes a built-in barbecue and offers ample space to create relaxing areas, an outdoor dining space or even a chill-out zone with open views.

The residential complex boasts a communal swimming pool surrounded by gardens, and the property also includes an exterior parking space.

Its location is excellent: in a quiet setting yet within walking distance to all amenities such as supermarkets, restaurants, schools, public transport and leisure areas. Both the beach and Zenia Boulevard are only a few minutes away on foot.

An ideal property either as a holiday home or as a rental investment in one of the most sought-after areas of Orihuela Costa.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 0 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 1</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Norte/Este</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium (m2): 40</feature>
                <feature>Distance sea: 1500</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168fad832_IMG_0662.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168fb83ad_IMG_0665.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f62b49_IMG_0653.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f6630c_IMG_0654.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168ebbe32_IMG_0618.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168eca896_IMG_0619.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168ece833_IMG_0620.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f1d46b_IMG_0627.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f32e25_IMG_0631.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f216f7_IMG_0628.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168eb7575_IMG_0617.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168ea162d_IMG_0613.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168ea2145_IMG_0614.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168edc45f_IMG_0621.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168ee04c6_IMG_0622.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168eeea12_IMG_0623.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168ef2d61_IMG_0624.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f0bc2f_IMG_0625.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f0ff1e_IMG_0626.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f2f08e_IMG_0629.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f406b5_IMG_0645.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f440d8_IMG_0647.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f5167b_IMG_0648.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f54fdc_IMG_0652.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f7e92b_IMG_0657.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f90de2_IMG_0658.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168f9c658_IMG_0660.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168fbf04a_IMG_0667.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4192RV/68b7168fd489b_IMG_0673.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3289</id>
            <date>2025-09-02 14:24:54</date>
            <ref>4193RV</ref>
            <price>149900</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Apartment</type>
            <town>Torrevieja</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.947802000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.710420000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Rocio del Mar</location_detail>
            <beds>1</beds><baths>1</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>64</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>E</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/apartments/tid4193RV</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/apartamentos/tid4193RV</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/appartements/tid4193RV</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/kvartiry/tid4193RV</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Este acogedor apartamento en 4ª planta de 1 dormitorio y 1 baño conserva su estado original pero se encuentra bien cuidado y listo para disfrutar desde el primer día. La vivienda cuenta con una superficie construida de aproximadamente 50 m² y ofrece un ambiente luminoso gracias a su orientación y a su terraza con vistas laterales al mar.

El salón-comedor es amplio y práctico, con salida directa a la terraza, un espacio perfecto para relajarse al aire libre con la brisa mediterránea. La cocina independiente mantiene el diseño original, bien distribuida y comunicada con la zona de estar a través de una ventana pasaplatos, aportando comodidad en el día a día.

El dormitorio principal dispone de armario empotrado y buena entrada de luz natural, mientras que el baño completo mantiene el estilo clásico de origen.

El edificio Lyon forma parte de la reconocida zona de Rocío del Mar y cuenta con piscina comunitaria y zona de aparcamiento, ofreciendo un entorno tranquilo y cómodo. Además, la urbanización se encuentra rodeada de todos los servicios necesarios: supermercados, restaurantes, transporte público y zonas de ocio.

Su ubicación es inmejorable, a escasos minutos a pie de la playa de Rocío del Mar y de Punta Prima, lo que convierte a esta vivienda en una opción ideal tanto como residencia habitual, segunda residencia vacacional o inversión de alquiler.

Una oportunidad para vivir cerca del mar en una de las zonas más demandadas de Torrevieja.</es><fr>Cet agréable appartement situé au 4ème étage, comprenant 1 chambre et 1 salle de bain, est dans son état d’origine mais bien entretenu, prêt à emménager et à profiter immédiatement. Avec une surface construite d’environ 50 m², il bénéficie d’une belle luminosité grâce à son orientation et à sa terrasse avec vue latérale sur la mer.

Le salon-salle à manger est spacieux et pratique, avec accès direct à la terrasse, un endroit idéal pour se détendre en plein air tout en profitant de la brise méditerranéenne. La cuisine indépendante conserve son style d’origine, bien agencée et reliée à la pièce de vie par un passe-plat, apportant confort et fonctionnalité au quotidien.

La chambre principale dispose d’une armoire encastrée et d’une belle lumière naturelle, tandis que la salle de bain conserve son style classique d’origine.

L’Edificio Lyon se situe dans le quartier recherché de Rocío del Mar et offre une piscine communautaire ainsi qu’une zone de stationnement, garantissant confort et tranquillité. L’urbanisation est entourée de tous les services nécessaires : supermarchés, restaurants, transports publics et zones de loisirs.

Sa situation est idéale, à quelques minutes à pied des plages de Rocío del Mar et de Punta Prima, ce qui en fait un choix parfait comme résidence principale, maison de vacances ou investissement locatif.</fr><ru>Уютные апартаменты на 4-м этаже с 1 спальней и 1 ванной комнатой сохранили свое оригинальное состояние, но находятся в хорошем состоянии и полностью готовы к заселению. Жилая площадь составляет около 50 м², а терраса с боковым видом на море и удачная ориентация обеспечивают хорошее естественное освещение.

Гостиная-столовая просторная и функциональная, с прямым выходом на террасу – идеальное место для отдыха на свежем воздухе и наслаждения средиземноморским бризом. Отдельная кухня сохранила оригинальный дизайн, удобно спланирована и соединена с зоной гостиной через окно-передатчик, что делает использование еще более комфортным.

Спальня оборудована встроенным шкафом и хорошо освещается естественным светом, а ванная комната выполнена в классическом стиле.

Эдифицио-Лион расположен в востребованном районе Росио-дель-Мар и предлагает общую зону с бассейном и парковкой, обеспечивая спокойствие и удобство. Урбанизация окружена всеми необходимыми услугами: супермаркетами, ресторанами, общественным транспортом и зонами отдыха.

Превосходное расположение – всего в нескольких минутах ходьбы от пляжей Росио-дель-Мар и Пунта-Прима. Отличный вариант как для постоянного проживания, так и для отдыха или инвестиций в аренду.</ru><en>This cozy 4th-floor apartment with 1 bedroom and 1 bathroom is in its original condition but well maintained, ready to move into and enjoy. With a built area of approximately 50 m², it offers a bright atmosphere thanks to its orientation and its terrace with side sea views.

The living-dining room is spacious and functional, with direct access to the terrace, an ideal place to relax outdoors while enjoying the Mediterranean breeze. The independent kitchen keeps its original design, well distributed and connected to the living area through a serving hatch, which adds comfort to daily life.

The bedroom includes a built-in wardrobe and receives plenty of natural light, while the bathroom maintains its classic original style.

Edificio Lyon, located in the sought-after area of Rocío del Mar, offers a community swimming pool and parking area, providing comfort and tranquility. The urbanization is surrounded by all necessary services: supermarkets, restaurants, public transport, and leisure facilities.

Its location is excellent, just a few minutes’ walk from Rocío del Mar and Punta Prima beaches, making this apartment an ideal option as a permanent residence, holiday home, or rental investment.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 6 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 4</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: 500</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c6cbbb9_IMG_0866.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c701824_T73A6887.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c70a0fb_T73A6889.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c6b0911_IMG_0864.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c6a02df_IMG_0862.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c6a59bc_IMG_0863.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c68388f_IMG_0858.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c68f553_IMG_0859.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c694058_IMG_0861.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c672d81_IMG_0853.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c67e7fc_IMG_0854.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c63766d_IMG_0843.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c64f9d1_IMG_0845.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c64a040_IMG_0844.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c633b22_IMG_0842.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c65aea6_IMG_0846.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c660e72_IMG_0847.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c66dad6_IMG_0849.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c6e6365_T73A6880.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b70a179960c_T73A6873.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4193RV/68b708c71781c_T73A6890.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3343</id>
            <date>2025-09-29 13:45:57</date>
            <ref>4197</ref>
            <price>2490000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Villa</type>
            <town>Torrevieja</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.960644000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.703939000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>La Veleta</location_detail>
            <beds>6</beds><baths>6</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>728</built>
                <plot>700</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>D</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/villas/tid4197</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/villas/tid4197</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/villas/tid4197</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/villy/tid4197</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Descubre esta espectacular villa independiente en venta en La Veleta, Torrevieja (Costa Blanca Sur), una de las zonas más exclusivas y demandadas por compradores internacionales que buscan una vivienda de lujo cerca del mar en España.

Construida sobre una parcela de 700 m², esta propiedad ofrece más de 700 m² de superficie construida, distribuidos en varias plantas y con acabados de la más alta calidad. Su arquitectura mediterránea, con techos de teja, vigas de madera y amplias terrazas, refleja el encanto tradicional de la Costa Blanca combinado con el confort moderno.

En la planta principal, la villa cuenta con un espacioso salón con chimenea, zonas de estar y comedor, una elegante sala de música y una cocina totalmente equipada con muebles de madera maciza y encimeras de granito. El interior destaca por su luminosidad, suelos de cerámica artesanal y detalles en hierro forjado.

La planta superior alberga dormitorios amplios y luminosos, entre ellos una suite principal con baño privado y terraza. En la buhardilla encontramos un espacio versátil, ideal como despacho o sala de ocio.

En el exterior, esta villa en venta en Torrevieja con piscina privada dispone de un precioso jardín mediterráneo con zona chill-out, barbacoa y horno de leña, perfectos para disfrutar del estilo de vida al aire libre durante todo el año. El sótano ofrece un garaje con capacidad para varios vehículos, trastero y sala de máquinas.

La urbanización La Veleta es conocida por su ambiente tranquilo y su excelente ubicación, a tan solo unos minutos a pie del mar y de las playas más bonitas de Torrevieja, con todos los servicios a su alrededor: restaurantes, supermercados, centros médicos y colegios internacionales.

Esta es una propiedad ideal para quienes buscan comprar una villa de lujo en la Costa Blanca, ya sea como residencia habitual, casa de vacaciones o inversión exclusiva en España.</es><fr>Découvrez cette villa individuelle de luxe à vendre à La Veleta, Torrevieja (Costa Blanca Sud), située dans l’un des quartiers les plus exclusifs et recherchés par les acheteurs étrangers qui souhaitent acheter une villa près de la mer en Espagne.

Édifiée sur un terrain de 700 m², la propriété offre plus de 700 m² construits, répartis sur plusieurs niveaux et combinant architecture méditerranéenne et confort moderne. Ses toits en tuiles, poutres apparentes et grandes terrasses lui confèrent un charme authentique et intemporel.

Le rez-de-chaussée comprend un vaste salon avec cheminée, une salle à manger élégante, un salon de musique et une cuisine entièrement équipée en bois massif avec plans de travail en granit. L’intérieur se distingue par ses matériaux nobles, ses sols en céramique artisanale et sa luminosité naturelle.

À l’étage, la villa dispose de chambres spacieuses et lumineuses, dont une suite parentale avec salle de bain privée et terrasse. Les combles offrent un espace polyvalent, idéal pour un bureau ou une salle de loisirs.

À l’extérieur, vous profiterez d’une piscine privée, de terrasses couvertes, d’un barbecue en briques et four à bois, ainsi que d’un jardin méditerranéen soigneusement aménagé. Le sous-sol comprend un grand garage pour plusieurs véhicules, un espace de rangement et une salle technique.

Située dans le prestigieux quartier résidentiel La Veleta, cette propriété offre calme, intimité et proximité de la mer, à quelques minutes seulement des plages les plus prisées de Torrevieja et de toutes les commodités : supermarchés, restaurants, écoles internationales et centres médicaux.

Une opportunité unique pour acheter une villa de luxe sur la Costa Blanca, parfaite comme résidence principale, maison de vacances ou investissement immobilier haut de gamme.

Mots-clés : villa de luxe à vendre à La Veleta, villa à vendre à Torrevieja, propriété de prestige Costa Blanca, maison avec piscine privée en Espagne, acheter villa près de la mer, immobilier Espagne.</fr><ru>Представляем роскошную отдельно стоящую виллу на продажу в Ла-Велета (Торревьеха, Коста-Бланка) — одном из самых престижных и спокойных районов города, идеально подходящем для тех, кто хочет купить дом у моря в Испании.

Вилла построена на участке 700 м² и имеет более 700 м² общей площади, распреелённой на нескольких уровнях. Архитектура выполнена в классическом средиземноморском стиле — с черепичной крышей, деревянными балками и просторными террасами, окружёнными зеленью.

На главном этаже расположены просторная гостиная с камином, изысканная столовая, музыкальная комната и полностью оборудованная кухня с мебелью из массива дерева и гранитными поверхностями. Интерьер наполнен светом и теплом, выполнен с использованием натуральных материалов и декоративной отделки ручной работы.

На втором этаже находятся большие и светлые спальни, включая главную спальню с собственной ванной комнатой и террасой. Мансардный этаж может быть использован как кабинет, библиотека или зона отдыха.

На участке расположены частный бассейн, крытые террасы, зона барбекю с печью на дровах и красивый сад в средиземноморском стиле. В цоколе находится гараж на несколько автомобилей, кладовая и техническое помещение.

Район Ла-Велета славится своей тишиной и близостью к морю — всего несколько минут ходьбы до лучших пляжей Торревьехи, ресторанов, супермаркетов и международных школ.

Отличная возможность купить виллу класса люкс в Испании, которая подойдёт как для постоянного проживания, так и для отдыха или инвестиций.
Ключевые слова: купить виллу в Торревьехе, вилла на продажу Ла-Велета, недвижимость на Коста-Бланке, дом с бассейном в Испании, роскошная недвижимость в Торревьехе.</ru><en>Discover this luxury detached villa for sale in La Veleta, Torrevieja (Costa Blanca South) — one of the most exclusive and sought-after areas for international buyers looking to buy a property near the sea in Spain.

Built on a 700 m² plot, this stunning home offers more than 700 m² of constructed area across several levels, combining elegant Mediterranean architecture with the comfort of a modern home. The exterior features traditional tiled roofs, wooden beams, and spacious terraces surrounded by lush greenery.

On the main floor, you’ll find a bright living room with fireplace, an elegant dining area, a charming music room, and a fully equipped kitchen finished in natural wood and granite. The interiors are warm and inviting, with handcrafted ceramic floors, ironwork details, and abundant natural light.

Upstairs, the villa features large, sunlit bedrooms, including a master suite with private bathroom and terrace. The attic level offers a versatile open space, perfect as an office or leisure area.

Outside, the property offers a private swimming pool, covered terraces, a built-in barbecue and wood oven, and a beautifully landscaped Mediterranean garden. The basement includes a spacious garage for multiple vehicles, storage, and a utility room.

Located in the prestigious La Veleta residential area, this property enjoys peace, privacy, and proximity to the sea — just a few minutes from Torrevieja’s best beaches, international schools, supermarkets, and restaurants.

A perfect opportunity for those seeking to buy a luxury villa in Spain — ideal as a permanent residence, holiday home, or exclusive investment on the Costa Blanca.
Keywords: luxury villa for sale in La Veleta, villa for sale in Torrevieja, Costa Blanca property for sale, Spanish villa near the sea, detached villa with private pool, buy villa in Spain.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 0 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: </feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Este</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: 200</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71bcbd67a_0104.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef716e361fe_T73A5829.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef716e3ec7f_T73A5825.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef716e4c55a_T73A5832.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef716e5bc4d_T73A5837.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef716e5f222_T73A5840.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7174260e3_DJI_0435.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef717c72beb_DJI_0449.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71996b63b_DJI_0410.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef719f125b3_DJI_0414.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71a55caf9_DJI_0428.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71ac2cbfd_DJI_0402.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71c03807a_0105.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71cabcf27_0108.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71cac020e_0109.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71d3553a4_0111.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71d35e86f_0110.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71d842df2_0113.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71e1965a3_0117.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71ebeecd0_0118.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71ec09e61_0119.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71f1c64f1_0120.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71fc876de_0123.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef71fc91cf0_0122.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7202e25fc_0125.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7202e3877_0126.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef720b8c0f7_0127.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef720b96519_0128.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7216c1228_0131.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7216ca92e_0130.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7216d238f_0132.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef721d39c3b_0135.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef722582073_0137.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef722b0d94e_0139.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef723053d30_0141.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef72354ff9f_0142.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef723907b9a_0144.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef723c8cdce_0145.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef723fd17fa_0146.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="40">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7244158ce_0148.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="41">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef72495ad45_0149.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="42">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef724ddba5a_0151.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="43">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7250ef76d_0152.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="44">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7255254a6_0154.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="45">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef725a13134_0155.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="46">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef725d80aa3_0157.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="47">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7261ac719_0159.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="48">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef7264978d7_0160.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="49">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef726826b65_0162.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="50">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4197/68ef726ce365b_0165.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3414</id>
            <date>2025-10-20 13:41:44</date>
            <ref>4199RV</ref>
            <price>187900</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Apartment</type>
            <town>Torrevieja</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>38.019934000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.656691000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>La Mata</location_detail>
            <beds>1</beds><baths>1</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>45</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>F</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/apartments/tid4199RV</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/apartamentos/tid4199RV</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/appartements/tid4199RV</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/kvartiry/tid4199RV</ru>
            </url><desc><es>A tan solo 200 metros de la playa de La Mata, en Torrevieja, se encuentra este precioso apartamento en venta, completamente reformado con materiales de alta calidad y un diseño moderno y funcional. La vivienda, situada en la urbanización Viñamar V, cuenta con 1 dormitorio, 1 baño, una superficie interior de 45 m² y una amplia terraza de 12 m² orientada al sur, ideal para disfrutar del sol durante todo el año. La terraza dispone de toldos, creando un espacio perfecto para relajarse al aire libre con privacidad y confort.
Este apartamento se vende totalmente amueblado y equipado con electrodomésticos, aire acondicionado y sistema de alarma, listo para entrar a vivir o comenzar a rentabilizar desde el primer día. Incluye además una plaza de garaje privada, un valor añadido muy apreciado en esta zona costera de alta demanda.

Ubicado dentro de una urbanización cerrada con piscina comunitaria y zonas comunes cuidadas, ofrece seguridad, tranquilidad y un entorno perfecto tanto para residencia habitual como para vacaciones. En los alrededores se encuentran todos los servicios necesarios: supermercados, restaurantes, farmacias, transporte público y zonas de ocio.

Gracias a su excelente ubicación junto al mar, su equipamiento completo y su alto potencial de inversión, esta propiedad representa una magnífica oportunidad para comprar un apartamento en La Mata, Torrevieja, ideal tanto como vivienda permanente como inversión en alquiler vacacional o de larga estancia.</es><fr>À seulement 200 mètres de la plage de La Mata, à Torrevieja, se trouve ce magnifique appartement à vendre, entièrement rénové avec des matériaux de haute qualité et un design moderne et fonctionnel. Il dispose d’une chambre, d’une salle de bain, de 45 m² habitables et d’une grande terrasse de 12 m² orientée plein sud, idéale pour profiter du soleil tout au long de l’année. La terrasse est équipée de stores, créant un espace extérieur confortable et privé pour se détendre.

L’appartement est vendu entièrement meublé et équipé avec électroménagers, climatisation et système d’alarme — prêt à emménager ou à être loué immédiatement. Il comprend également une place de parking privée, un atout très recherché dans cette zone côtière prisée.

Situé dans la résidence Viñamar V, avec piscine communautaire et espaces communs bien entretenus, ce logement offre sécurité, tranquillité et un cadre idéal, que ce soit pour y vivre toute l’année ou pour les vacances. À proximité se trouvent tous les services : supermarchés, restaurants, pharmacies, transports publics et loisirs.

Grâce à son emplacement privilégié près de la mer, son excellent équipement et son fort potentiel locatif, cet appartement représente une excellente opportunité pour acheter une propriété à La Mata, Torrevieja, qu’il s’agisse d’une résidence principale ou d’un investissement sur la Costa Blanca.</fr><ru>Всего в 200 метрах от пляжа Ла-Мата (Торревьеха) расположена эта прекрасная квартира на продажу, полностью отремонтированная с использованием высококачественных материалов и современного дизайна. В квартире есть 1 спальня, 1 ванная комната, жилая площадь 45 м² и солнечная терраса площадью 12 м², ориентированная на юг — идеальное место, чтобы наслаждаться морским климатом круглый год. Терраса оборудована тентами, что создаёт комфортное и уединённое пространство для отдыха на свежем воздухе.

Квартира продаётся полностью меблированной и оснащённой бытовой техникой, кондиционером и сигнализацией — готова к заселению или сдаче в аренду с первого дня. В стоимость также входит частное парковочное место, очень ценное преимущество в этом прибрежном районе.

Жилой комплекс Viñamar V предлагает общий бассейн и ухоженные зоны отдыха, обеспечивая безопасность, спокойствие и приятную атмосферу как для постоянного проживания, так и для отпуска. В шаговой доступности находятся супермаркеты, рестораны, аптеки, общественный транспорт и зоны отдыха.

Благодаря своему отличному расположению рядом с морем, современному оснащению и высокому инвестиционному потенциалу, эта квартира в Ла-Мате — отличная возможность купить недвижимость в Торревьехе для жизни или для получения дохода от аренды на Коста-Бланке.</ru><en>Just 200 meters from La Mata Beach in Torrevieja, this beautiful apartment for sale offers modern design, high-quality finishes, and an unbeatable location by the sea. The property features 1 bedroom, 1 bathroom, 45 m² of interior space, and a sunny 12 m² south-facing terrace — perfect to enjoy the Mediterranean climate all year round. The terrace is equipped with awnings, providing a private and comfortable outdoor area for relaxation.

The apartment is sold fully furnished and equipped with appliances, air conditioning, and an alarm system, ready to move in or start renting out immediately. It also includes a private parking space, a highly valued feature in this popular coastal area.

Located in the well-known Viñamar V residential complex, the property offers access to a communal swimming pool and beautifully maintained common areas, providing a peaceful and secure environment both for permanent living and holidays. The area offers all services within walking distance — supermarkets, restaurants, pharmacies, public transport, and leisure options.

Thanks to its excellent location near the sea, modern features, and strong rental potential, this apartment in La Mata is an ideal opportunity to buy a property in Torrevieja for personal use or as an investment on the Costa Blanca.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 13 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 0</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: 200</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920f3cf9b1_Gemini_Generated_Image_vfq0dvfq0dvfq0dv.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d09be5aa_IMG_0099.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d09e4d1b_IMG_0104.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d0a402c9_IMG_0121.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920e99a63e_IMG_0666.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920e99b732_IMG_0667.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920ec107ec_IMG_0668.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920ec11e92_IMG_0669.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920ee97808_IMG_0677.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920ee988dc_IMG_0678.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920f124b6a_IMG_0679.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920db56d71_IMG_0651.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920db370e1_IMG_0646.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920db45e46_IMG_0647.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920db47cd5_IMG_0648.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920e4bf438_IMG_0661.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920e4c073a_IMG_0662.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920e754d8f_IMG_0663.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920e7538e7_IMG_0664.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920db238ef_IMG_0641.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920db21627_IMG_0642.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920db344dd_IMG_0643.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920f1307f6_IMG_0681.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920dfe975e_IMG_0655.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920dd86934_IMG_0654.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920dfeabc9_IMG_0656.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920e25051b_IMG_0657.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920dd80dc7_IMG_0653.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920e25a4e4_IMG_0658.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920f3a02df_IMG_0683.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920f3b2cd0_Gemini_Generated_Image_d2cbud2cbud2cbud.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920f3bd5e3_Gemini_Generated_Image_ezo95vezo95vezo9.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920f3c4b41_Gemini_Generated_Image_i72e7oi72e7oi72e.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920f3e3b02_Gemini_Generated_Image_wacumvwacumvwacu.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920f3e1d34_Gemini_Generated_Image_wzwkb3wzwkb3wzwk.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d09da9d2_IMG_0101.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d09bf85a_IMG_0100.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d09eb984_IMG_0107.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d0a0d1f6_IMG_0108.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="40">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d0a0f286_IMG_0110.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="41">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d0a1e3fe_IMG_0112.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="42">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d09d3207_IMG_0102.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="43">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d0a2abf2_IMG_0113.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="44">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d0a2f2f2_IMG_0115.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="45">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d0a47189_IMG_0119.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="46">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d0a6c2c1_IMG_0126.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="47">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d0a62a27_IMG_0125.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="48">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68f7985daed5a_1757782540122.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="49">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/694920f3aafd2_IMG_0686.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="50">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4199RV/68ff9d0a7428c_IMG_0128.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3426</id>
            <date>2025-10-24 16:47:08</date>
            <ref>4200</ref>
            <price>275900</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Townhouse</type>
            <town>Orihuela Costa</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.938080000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.748369000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Villamartin</location_detail>
            <beds>3</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>98</built>
                <plot>72</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>F</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/townhouses/tid4200</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/adosados/tid4200</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/maisons-de-villes/tid4200</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/tounkhausy/tid4200</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Precioso dúplex tipo quad en esquina situado en la reconocida urbanización Vista Azul, una de las más exclusivas de Villamartin, Orihuela Costa. Esta vivienda combina confort, estilo mediterráneo y una ubicación privilegiada, en un entorno tranquilo y familiar cerca de todos los servicios esenciales.

Con 90 m² construidos sobre una parcela de 120 m², destaca por su orientación suroeste, que garantiza sol y luminosidad durante todo el año. En la planta baja se encuentra un amplio salón-comedor con acceso directo a la terraza, una cocina independiente totalmente equipada, un dormitorio ideal para invitados o despacho y un baño completo. En la planta superior se ubican dos dormitorios con armarios empotrados, un segundo baño y una escalera que conduce al solárium privado de 20 m², perfecto para disfrutar del sol, relajarse o contemplar las vistas despejadas.

La vivienda está en excelente estado y equipada con aire acondicionado, toldos, puerta de seguridad y aparcamiento privado dentro de la parcela. La amplia terraza que rodea la casa ofrece zonas de comedor y relax al aire libre, ideales para aprovechar el clima mediterráneo durante todo el año.

La urbanización Vista Azul ofrece magníficas zonas comunes con dos piscinas (una cubierta), jacuzzi, sauna y gimnasio, lo que la convierte en una de las comunidades más completas y valoradas de Villamartin.

Ubicada junto al Campo de Golf Villamartin, cerca de los centros comerciales La Zenia Boulevard y Playa Flamenca, y a solo 3 km de las playas de Orihuela Costa, esta propiedad es ideal para quienes buscan comprar un dúplex en Villamartin o invertir en una vivienda en venta en la Costa Blanca.

Una vivienda con encanto, lista para entrar a vivir, perfecta tanto como residencia habitual como para comprar como segunda vivienda o inversión inmobiliaria en Orihuela Costa.</es><fr>Superbe duplex d’angle de style méditerranéen situé dans la résidence exclusive Vista Azul, l’une des plus prisées de Villamartin, Orihuela Costa. Ce bien allie confort, élégance et emplacement idéal dans un environnement calme et familial, à proximité de tous les services essentiels.

Avec 90 m² construits sur un terrain de 120 m², la propriété bénéficie d’une orientation sud-ouest assurant une luminosité naturelle tout au long de la journée. Le rez-de-chaussée comprend un salon-salle à manger lumineux avec accès direct à la terrasse, une cuisine indépendante entièrement équipée, une chambre parfaite pour les invités ou comme bureau, ainsi qu’une salle de bain complète. À l’étage, deux chambres avec placards intégrés, une deuxième salle de bain et un accès au solarium privé de 20 m², idéal pour se détendre ou profiter du soleil et de la vue dégagée.

La maison est en excellent état et équipée de la climatisation, de stores, d’une porte de sécurité et d’un parking privé sur la parcelle. La terrasse spacieuse qui entoure la maison offre plusieurs espaces extérieurs pour manger et se relaxer, parfaits pour profiter du climat méditerranéen toute l’année.

La résidence Vista Azul dispose de magnifiques installations communes : deux piscines (dont une couverte), jacuzzi, sauna et salle de sport, faisant de ce complexe l’un des plus complets et recherchés de Villamartin.

Située à proximité du golf de Villamartin, des centres commerciaux La Zenia Boulevard et Playa Flamenca, et à seulement 3 km des plages d’Orihuela Costa, cette propriété est idéale pour ceux qui souhaitent acheter un duplex à Villamartin ou investir dans un bien immobilier à vendre sur la Costa Blanca.

Une maison pleine de charme, prête à emménager, parfaite comme résidence principale, maison de vacances ou investissement immobilier à Orihuela Costa.</fr><ru>Прекрасный угловой дуплекс, расположенный в эксклюзивной урбанизации Виста-Асул, одной из самых престижных в районе Вильямартин (Ориуэла-Коста). Дом сочетает в себе средиземноморский стиль, комфорт и отличное расположение — тихий семейный район рядом со всеми удобствами.

Площадь дома составляет 90 м², участок — 120 м². Юго-западная ориентация обеспечивает солнечное освещение на протяжении всего дня. На первом этаже находится просторная гостиная-столовая с выходом на террасу, полностью оборудованная кухня, спальня (подходит для гостей или под кабинет) и ванная комната. На втором этаже — две спальни со встроенными шкафами, вторая ванная комната и выход на частный солярий площадью 20 м², где можно отдыхать, загорать и наслаждаться панорамными видами.

Дом находится в отличном состоянии, оснащён кондиционером, маркизами, надёжной входной дверью и частной парковкой на участке. Просторная терраса вокруг дома предлагает уютные зоны отдыха и обеденные пространства на свежем воздухе — идеальное место, чтобы наслаждаться мягким климатом Коста-Бланки круглый год.

Урбанизация Виста-Асул предлагает отличные зоны общего пользования: два бассейна (один крытый), джакузи, сауна и спортзал, что делает её одной из самых привлекательных резиденций в Вильямартин.

Расположен рядом с полем для гольфа Вильямартин, недалеко от торговых центров Ла-Зения-Бульвар и Плая-Фламенка, всего в 3 км от пляжей Ориуэла-Коста. Этот объект идеально подойдёт тем, кто хочет купить дуплекс в Вильямартин или инвестировать в недвижимость на продажу на Коста-Бланке.

Очаровательный дом, полностью готовый к заселению, идеально подходит как для постоянного проживания, так и для покупки в качестве второго дома или инвестиции в Ориуэла-Коста.</ru><en>Beautiful corner quad-style duplex located in the exclusive Vista Azul Residential, one of the most desirable developments in Villamartin, Orihuela Costa. This home perfectly combines Mediterranean style, comfort and an excellent location within a quiet, family-friendly environment close to all essential amenities.

With 90 m² of built area on a 120 m² plot, the property enjoys a southwest orientation, providing plenty of natural light all day long. The ground floor offers a bright living-dining room with direct access to the terrace, a fully equipped independent kitchen, one bedroom ideal for guests or a home office, and a complete bathroom. The upper floor features two bedrooms with fitted wardrobes, a second bathroom, and access to a 20 m² private solarium, perfect for sunbathing, relaxing or enjoying open views.

The property is in excellent condition and equipped with air conditioning, awnings, security door and private parking inside the plot. The spacious terrace surrounding the house provides several outdoor dining and chill-out areas, ideal to enjoy the Mediterranean climate all year round.

The Vista Azul complex offers exceptional communal facilities including two swimming pools (one covered), jacuzzi, sauna and gym, making it one of the most complete and sought-after communities in Villamartin.

Located next to Villamartin Golf Course, close to La Zenia Boulevard and Playa Flamenca, and only 3 km from the beaches of Orihuela Costa, this home is perfect for those looking to buy a duplex in Villamartin or invest in a property for sale on the Costa Blanca.

A charming property, ready to move into — ideal as a permanent home, a holiday residence or a real estate investment in Orihuela Costa.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 6 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 0</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur/Oeste</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium (m2): 26</feature>
                <feature>Distance sea: 2500</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9027a6b02_IMG_0009.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90294fc70_IMG_0083.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9027d5a34_IMG_0015.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9027dccc8_IMG_0016.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9027f158a_IMG_0017.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9027c527a_IMG_0013.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9027b0f6c_IMG_0012.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff902802d62_IMG_0021.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff902813353_IMG_0026.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90282dfe3_IMG_0027.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90284433b_IMG_0030.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028400a8_IMG_0031.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff902859d7d_IMG_0032.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90285da51_IMG_0033.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff902869c7d_IMG_0036.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90286d580_IMG_0037.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90287a8d1_IMG_0038.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff902886a09_IMG_0040.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90289467a_IMG_0042.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028966ae_IMG_0044.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028a481d_IMG_0046.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028a601b_IMG_0047.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028b4252_IMG_0049.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028b5525_IMG_0050.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028cdd1d_IMG_0051.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028c52e2_IMG_0053.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028d4672_IMG_0055.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028deb00_IMG_0056.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028f0bfe_IMG_0058.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9028efaf0_IMG_0060.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90290b5e2_IMG_0062.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90290c3a3_IMG_0063.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90291ac1f_IMG_0066.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90291c113_IMG_0070.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90281941c_IMG_0022.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90293589c_IMG_0075.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff902944b83_IMG_0077.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90295e825_IMG_0085.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90295ff9e_IMG_0089 2.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="40">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90296f298_IMG_0091.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="41">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff9029709fd_IMG_0092.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="42">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90297f78c_IMG_0093.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="43">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4200/68ff90293480d_IMG_0073.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3483</id>
            <date>2025-11-10 11:02:28</date>
            <ref>4202</ref>
            <price>670000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Villa</type>
            <town>Orihuela Costa</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.935007000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.774963000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Las Filipinas</location_detail>
            <beds>5</beds><baths>3</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>366</built>
                <plot>1510</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>E</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/villas/tid4202</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/villas/tid4202</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/villas/tid4202</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/villy/tid4202</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Magnífico chalet independiente en Las Filipinas (urb. Villamartín), situado sobre una amplia parcela de 1.510 m² que ofrece total privacidad y un entorno natural privilegiado. Con 366 m² construidos, esta vivienda combina amplitud, comodidad y funcionalidad, distribuyéndose en cinco dormitorios, tres baños, un luminoso salón y un comedor independiente, ideales para una vida familiar confortable.

La propiedad cuenta con garaje cerrado y trastero, además de una espectacular piscina privada orientada al sur que disfruta del sol durante todo el día. El jardín, cuidadosamente ajardinado, rodea la vivienda y crea un ambiente tranquilo y verde, perfecto para el relax o para disfrutar al aire libre.

Entre sus características destacan la calefacción individual, amplios espacios interiores y exteriores, y una distribución pensada para el máximo confort.

Ubicada a solo 4-5 km de las playas de la Costa Blanca Sur (unos 8-10 minutos en coche), esta vivienda se encuentra también muy cerca del centro comercial La Zenia Boulevard, con una gran variedad de tiendas, restaurantes y zonas de ocio. La urbanización está perfectamente comunicada con la autopista AP-7 y la carretera N-332. En las inmediaciones hay supermercados, bares, restaurantes y varios campos de golf, lo que convierte esta propiedad en una excelente opción de compra tanto para residencia habitual como para vacaciones o inversión.</es><fr>Cette magnifique maison est située dans le quartier de Las Filipinas (urbanisation Villamartín) sur un vaste terrain de 1 510 m², offrant intimité et un environnement extérieur exceptionnel. La propriété dispose de 366 m² construits, comprenant cinq chambres, trois salles de bain, un salon et une salle à manger, garantissant confort et fonctionnalité pour toute la famille. Elle comprend également un garage et un débarras, offrant des espaces supplémentaires pour le rangement et les véhicules.

Parmi ses atouts figurent le chauffage individuel et une piscine privée orientée au sud, qui bénéficie du soleil toute la journée, parfaite pour la détente et le plaisir pendant les mois les plus chauds. Le jardin entourant la maison complète un cadre paisible et verdoyant, idéal pour se reposer ou profiter de la vie en plein air.

La maison se trouve à environ 4 à 5 km des plages de la Costa Blanca Sud, soit un trajet en voiture d’environ 8 à 10 minutes. Le centre commercial très prisé La Zenia Boulevard est à seulement 5 à 8 minutes en voiture, offrant un large choix de boutiques, restaurants et loisirs. En termes de transport et d’accès, l’urbanisation est bien reliée à l’autoroute AP‑7 et à la route N‑332. De plus, les supermarchés, restaurants, bars et services essentiels sont accessibles à pied ou en quelques minutes, et plusieurs terrains de golf se trouvent à proximité, rendant la zone particulièrement attractive pour les résidents permanents comme pour les vacanciers.</fr><ru>Этот великолепный дом расположен в районе Лас Филипинас (Вильямартин) на большой территории площадью 1 510 м², что обеспечивает уединение и прекрасное наружное пространство. Площадь дома составляет 366 м² и включает пять спален, три ванные комнаты, гостиную и столовую, обеспечивая комфорт и функциональность для всей семьи. Также имеется гараж и кладовая, предоставляющие дополнительное пространство для хранения и автомобилей.

Среди удобств — индивидуальное отопление и частный бассейн, ориентированный на юг, который получает солнечный свет в течение всего дня, идеально подходящий для отдыха и наслаждения в теплое время года. Сад вокруг дома создает спокойную и зеленую атмосферу, идеально подходящую для отдыха на свежем воздухе.

Дом находится примерно в 4–5 км от пляжей Коста-Бланка-Сур, что занимает около 8–10 минут на автомобиле. Популярный торговый центр La Zenia Boulevard находится всего в 5–8 минутах езды, предлагая широкий выбор магазинов, ресторанов и развлечений. В плане транспорта и доступа урбанизация хорошо связана с автомагистралью AP‑7 и дорогой N‑332. Кроме того, в пешей доступности находятся супермаркеты, рестораны, бары и основные услуги, а также несколько гольф‑полей поблизости, что делает район особенно привлекательным как для постоянного проживания, так и для отдыха.</ru><en>This magnificent house is located in the Las Filipinas area (Villamartín urbanization) on a large plot of 1,510 m², offering privacy and an exceptional outdoor environment. The property has 366 m² of built space, with five bedrooms, three bathrooms, a living room, and a dining room, providing comfort and functionality for the whole family. It also includes a garage and a storage room, offering additional space for storage and vehicles.

Among its features are individual heating and a private south-facing pool that enjoys sunlight all day, perfect for relaxation and enjoyment during the warmer months. The garden surrounding the house completes a peaceful and green environment, ideal for rest or outdoor living.

The property is approximately 4–5 km from the beaches of Costa Blanca South, which is about an 8–10 minute drive. The popular La Zenia Boulevard shopping center is just 5–8 minutes away by car, offering a wide range of shops, restaurants, and entertainment. Regarding transport and access, the urbanization is well connected to the AP‑7 motorway and the N‑332 road. Additionally, supermarkets, restaurants, bars, and essential services are within walking distance or just a few minutes away, and several golf courses are nearby, making the area particularly attractive for both permanent residents and vacationers.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 0 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: </feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: 4000</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfde73f1_T73A8699.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe0835e_T73A8703.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfde17ce_T73A8691.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe0353f_T73A8704.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe136f0_T73A8706.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd46d7d_T73A8639.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd378d5_T73A8638.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfce05aa_T73A8623.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfcedea9_T73A8625.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd11983_T73A8630.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd12d4d_T73A8634.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd24db3_T73A8635.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd32a96_T73A8636.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd646f2_T73A8658.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe3dbfd_T73A8710.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe342e6_T73A8715.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe450d0_T73A8718.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe57d87_T73A8722.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe5fa7e_T73A8726.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe68654_T73A8732.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe838e1_T73A8736.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe94b5e_T73A8741.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe93a30_T73A8743.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfea4a2b_T73A8745.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfea5b11_T73A8746.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfeb5efa_T73A8747.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe79fb5_T73A8734.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfec02a6_T73A8754.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe226e7_T73A8707.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfe23b7e_T73A8709.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfec5f70_T73A8756.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfedb9af_T73A8758.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfee16b8_T73A8763.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcff3191b_T73A8775.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfeec04a_T73A8765.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcff079f4_T73A8766.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcff17aec_T73A8769.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcff2ccad_T73A8773.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcff127d6_T73A8768.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="40">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcff6a585_T73A8785.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="41">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcff3dc83_T73A8777.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="42">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcff41e0b_T73A8778.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="43">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcff58d5c_T73A8781.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="44">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcff5ba8d_T73A8784.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="45">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd4a00c_T73A8646.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="46">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd5d6d7_T73A8660.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="47">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd77399_T73A8667.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="48">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd708d1_T73A8663.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="49">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfd836d8_T73A8673.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="50">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4202/6911bcfda2e78_T73A8680.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3507</id>
            <date>2025-11-26 09:47:06</date>
            <ref>4203</ref>
            <price>360000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Penthouse</type>
            <town>Torrevieja</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.965697700000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.738682400000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Los Balcones</location_detail>
            <beds>3</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>84</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>C</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/penthouse/tid4203</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/atico/tid4203</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/penthouse/tid4203</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/pentkhausy/tid4203</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Este exclusivo ático en Mirasal, ubicado en la prestigiosa zona de Los Balcones (Torrevieja), destaca por su diseño moderno, su luminosidad y su privilegiada posición en el punto más elevado del residencial. Gracias a esta ubicación única, la vivienda disfruta de vistas panorámicas a Torrevieja, al Mediterráneo y a las emblemáticas Salinas Rosas, uno de los paisajes naturales más icónicos de la Costa Blanca.

El interior del ático ofrece un ambiente amplio y elegante, con una cocina abierta de estilo minimalista y un salón lleno de luz que conecta directamente con una terraza espaciosa orientada hacia la piscina infinity y los jardines del complejo. Los grandes ventanales permiten una transición fluida entre interior y exterior, potenciando la sensación de espacio y bienestar.

El gran protagonista es su espectacular solárium privado de 75m2, un rooftop diseñado para disfrutar del clima mediterráneo durante todo el año. Dispone de zonas de descanso, comedor exterior, barra y pérgolas, convirtiéndose en un espacio perfecto tanto para relajarse como para recibir invitados. Desde aquí, las vistas abiertas a las salinas y a toda la ciudad de Torrevieja son sencillamente incomparables.

Incluye además una cómoda plaza de aparcamiento subterráneo y trastero.

El residencial Mirasal es conocido por su arquitectura contemporánea, sus amplias zonas verdes y su impresionante piscina de estilo infinity. Su ubicación en Los Balcones ofrece tranquilidad, cercanía a todos los servicios, acceso rápido a áreas deportivas, supermercados, zonas naturales y a tan solo unos minutos en coche de las playas de Torrevieja.
Este ático es una oportunidad única para quienes buscan una vivienda moderna, exclusiva y con unas vistas privilegiadas en uno de los mejores residenciales de la Costa Blanca.</es><fr>Ce penthouse exclusif situé dans la prestigieuse zone de Los Balcones à Torrevieja, au sein du complexe Mirasal, se distingue par son design contemporain, sa luminosité exceptionnelle et son emplacement privilégié au point le plus élevé de la résidence. Grâce à cette position dominante, la propriété offre des vues panoramiques sur Torrevieja, la mer Méditerranée et le célèbre Lac Rose, l’un des paysages naturels les plus emblématiques de la Costa Blanca.

À l’intérieur, le penthouse propose une atmosphère élégante et spacieuse, avec une cuisine ouverte moderne et un salon lumineux relié à une grande terrasse avec vue sur la piscine à débordement et les jardins paysagers du complexe. Les larges baies vitrées créent une transition fluide entre les espaces intérieurs et extérieurs, renforçant la sensation d’ouverture et de bien-être.

Le véritable atout de cette propriété est son spectaculaire solarium privé de 75m2 sur le toit, entièrement conçu pour profiter du climat méditerranéen tout au long de l’année. Il comprend des espaces détente, une salle à manger extérieure, un coin bar et des pergolas — un lieu parfait pour se relaxer ou recevoir des invités. Depuis ce rooftop, les vues ouvertes sur le Lac Rose et sur toute la ville de Torrevieja sont absolument exceptionnelles.

Il comprend également une place de parking souterrain confortable et un débarras.

Mirasal est reconnu pour son architecture contemporaine, ses vastes zones vertes et son impressionnante piscine à débordement. Situé dans Los Balcones, il offre tranquillité, proximité de tous les services, accès rapide aux installations sportives, supermarchés, espaces naturels et se trouve à seulement quelques minutes en voiture des plages de Torrevieja.

Une opportunité unique pour ceux qui recherchent un penthouse moderne, exclusif et offrant des vues privilégiées dans l’un des meilleurs complexes résidentiels de la Costa Blanca.</fr><ru>Этот эксклюзивный пентхаус в жилом комплексе Мирасаль, расположенном в престижном районе Лос-Бальконес (Торревьеха), выделяется современным дизайном, яркими интерьерами и уникальным расположением на самой верхней точке участка. Благодаря этой возвышенной позиции открываются панорамные виды на Торревьеху, Средиземное море и знаменитое Розовое солёное озеро, одно из самых необычных природных мест на Коста-Бланке.

Внутреннее пространство создаёт атмосферу уюта и элегантности: современная открытая кухня соединена со светлой гостиной, которая выходит на просторную террасу с видом на инфинити-бассейн и ухоженные сады комплекса. Панорамные окна обеспечивают плавный переход между интерьером и зонами отдыха на свежем воздухе, усиливая ощущение простора и комфорта.

Главная особенность объекта — впечатляющий частный солярий площадью 75 м2, полностью оборудованный для круглогодичного отдыха. Здесь есть зоны для релаксации, открытая обеденная зона, барная стойка и перголы — идеальное место для спокойного отдыха или приёма гостей. С солярия открываются потрясающие виды на Розовое озеро и весь город Торревьеха.

В стоимость также входят подземная парковка и кладовая комната.

Жилой комплекс Мирасаль известен своей современной архитектурой, обширными зелёными зонами и эффектным инфинити-бассейном. Его расположение в Лос-Бальконес обеспечивает тишину, удобную близость ко всем сервисам, быстрый доступ к спортивным объектам, супермаркетам и природным зонам, а также всего несколько минут езды до лучших пляжей Торревьехи.

Идеальный выбор для тех, кто ищет современный и эксклюзивный пентхаус с привилегированными видами в одном из лучших жилых комплексов Коста-Бланки.</ru><en>This exclusive penthouse in Mirasal, located in the prestigious Los Balcones area of Torrevieja, stands out for its contemporary design, exceptional brightness and privileged position at the highest point of the residential complex. Thanks to this elevated location, the property enjoys panoramic views over Torrevieja, the Mediterranean Sea and the iconic Pink Salt Lake, one of the most unique natural landscapes on the Costa Blanca.

Inside, the penthouse offers a spacious and elegant atmosphere, with a modern open-plan kitchen and a bright living area connected to a generous terrace overlooking the infinity-style swimming pool and landscaped gardens. Large floor-to-ceiling windows create a seamless transition between indoor and outdoor spaces, enhancing the sense of openness and wellbeing.

The highlight of the property is its spectacular 75m2 private rooftop solarium, fully designed for year-round outdoor living. The space includes chill-out areas, an outdoor dining space, a bar area and pergolas, making it perfect for relaxing or entertaining guests. From here, the open views of the salt lake and the entire city of Torrevieja are simply extraordinary.

It also includes a convenient underground parking space and a storage room.

Mirasal is known for its contemporary architecture, large green areas and impressive infinity-style pool. Its location in Los Balcones offers tranquillity, proximity to all services, quick access to sports facilities, supermarkets and natural surroundings, and is just a short drive from Torrevieja’s best beaches.

A unique opportunity for those seeking a modern and exclusive penthouse with privileged views in one of the finest residential complexes on the Costa Blanca.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 20 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 1</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Este</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium (m2): 75</feature>
                <feature>Distance sea: 4000</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c685a9cf8_IMG_0467.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c68480161_IMG_0401.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6858e3c6_IMG_0459.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6859f0cd_IMG_0464.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6846f3e9_IMG_0407.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c68486f7c_IMG_0408.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c68491aec_IMG_0411.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6849a2ea_IMG_0414.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c684a4bf2_IMG_0415.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c684ab13d_IMG_0416.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c684b695e_IMG_0417.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c684bc8b5_IMG_0418.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c684c7d29_IMG_0419.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c684cd69d_IMG_0420.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c684d84b3_IMG_0428.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c684de32a_IMG_0429.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c684e8ec7_IMG_0430.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c684eee20_IMG_0431.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c68505ec3_IMG_0432.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/69384ba534f97_zoutmeer.JPG</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6850b57b_IMG_0433.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c68517251_IMG_0434.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6851be4c_IMG_0435.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c68527eca_IMG_0438.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6852d04e_IMG_0440.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c685397e2_IMG_0441.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6853dabe_IMG_0442.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6854aa25_IMG_0445.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6854ebe3_IMG_0446.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6855b934_IMG_0447.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6855f909_IMG_0449.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6856c441_IMG_0451.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4203/6926c6856ff88_IMG_0452.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3512</id>
            <date>2025-11-28 22:11:25</date>
            <ref>4205</ref>
            <price>715000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Penthouse</type>
            <town>Torrevieja</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.945063100000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.706681000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Punta Prima</location_detail>
            <beds>2</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>175</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>E</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/penthouse/tid4205</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/atico/tid4205</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/penthouse/tid4205</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/pentkhausy/tid4205</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Presentamos este impresionante ático de lujo ubicado en el exclusivo residencial Sea Senses, uno de los complejos más demandados de Punta Prima. Con una inmejorable orientación sureste y vistas panorámicas al Mediterráneo, esta propiedad ofrece un estilo de vida privilegiado junto al mar. 

La vivienda cuenta con 2 dormitorios y 2 baños, distribuidos de forma moderna y funcional para garantizar el máximo confort. Desde luminoso salon se abre a una encantadora terraza de 12 m², perfecta para disfrutar del amanecer y de la brisa marina. El mayor atractivo de este ático es su espectacular solárium privado de 83 m², equipado con jacuzzi y zonas de relax, un auténtico oasis privado con vistas infinitas al mar, ideal para disfrutar del clima mediterráneo durante todo el año. La propiedad incluye plaza de parking subterráneo y trastero, aportando comodidad y espacio adicional de almacenamiento. 

El residencial Sea Senses es uno de los complejos más prestigiosos de la Costa Blanca Sur. Ofrece zonas comunes de primer nivel, con piscinas infinitas frente al mar, gimnasio, spa, jacuzzis, pistas deportivas y áreas ajardinadas. Un entorno diseñado para disfrutar de privacidad, lujo y bienestar. 

Situado en la reconocida zona de Punta Prima, este ático se encuentra a pocos pasos de la playa y rodeado de servicios durante todo el año: supermercados, restaurantes, cafeterías, transporte público y zonas de ocio. Además, está a corta distancia de centros comerciales como Zenia Boulevard, prestigiosos campos de golf y los principales accesos a las ciudades de Torrevieja y Orihuela Costa. 
Una vivienda única, donde la exclusividad, el confort y las vistas al mar se combinan para ofrecer una experiencia de vida inigualable.</es><fr>Nous vous présentons ce superbe penthouse de luxe situé dans la résidence exclusive Sea Senses, l’un des complexes les plus prisés de Punta Prima. Avec une orientation sud-est exceptionnelle et des vues panoramiques sur la Méditerranée, cette propriété offre un style de vie privilégié en bord de mer.

Le logement dispose de 2 chambres et 2 salles de bains, conçues dans un style moderne et fonctionnel pour garantir un confort optimal. Depuis le salon lumineux, vous accédez à une charmante terrasse de 12 m², idéale pour profiter du lever du soleil et de la brise marine.

L’atout majeur de cet attique est son spectaculaire solarium privé de 83 m², équipé d’un jacuzzi et de zones de détente — un véritable oasis privé avec des vues infinies sur la mer, parfait pour profiter du climat méditerranéen toute l’année.

La propriété comprend également une place de parking souterrain et un débarras, offrant confort et espace de rangement supplémentaire.

La résidence Sea Senses est l’une des plus prestigieuses de la Costa Blanca Sud, offrant des espaces communs haut de gamme : piscines à débordement face à la mer, salle de sport, spa, jacuzzis, terrains de sport et jardins paysagers. Un environnement pensé pour offrir intimité, luxe et bien-être.

Situé dans le quartier renommé de Punta Prima, ce penthouse se trouve à quelques pas de la plage et à proximité de tous les services tout au long de l’année : supermarchés, restaurants, cafés, transports publics et zones de loisirs. Il est également proche du centre commercial Zenia Boulevard, de prestigieux parcours de golf et des principaux accès vers Torrevieja et Orihuela Costa.

Une propriété unique où exclusivité, confort et vues sur la mer se combinent pour offrir une expérience de vie incomparable.</fr><ru>Представляем этот впечатляющий роскошный пентхаус, расположенный в эксклюзивном жилом комплексе Sea Senses — одном из самых востребованных комплексов района Пунта-Прима. С превосходной юго-восточной ориентацией и панорамными видами на Средиземное море эта недвижимость предлагает привилегированный образ жизни у самой кромки моря.

Квартира состоит из 2 спален и 2 ванных комнат, спроектированных в современном и функциональном стиле для обеспечения максимального комфорта. Из светлой гостиной есть выход на очаровательную террасу площадью 12 м² — идеальное место, чтобы наслаждаться рассветом и морским бризом.

Главной особенностью этого пентхауса является его впечатляющий приватный солярий площадью 83 м², оборудованный джакузи и зонами отдыха — настоящий частный оазис с бескрайними видами на море, идеальный для наслаждения средиземноморским климатом круглый год.

В стоимость также входят подземное парковочное место и кладовая, что обеспечивает удобство и дополнительное пространство для хранения.

Жилой комплекс Sea Senses является одним из самых престижных на юге Коста-Бланки, предлагая зоны общего пользования высшего уровня: инфинити-бассейны с видом на море, тренажёрный зал, спа, джакузи, спортивные площадки и озеленённые территории. Всё создано для максимальной приватности, роскоши и благополучия.

Пентхаус расположен в престижном районе Пунта-Прима, всего в нескольких шагах от пляжа и рядом со всеми необходимыми услугами круглый год: супермаркетами, ресторанами, кафе, общественным транспортом и зонами отдыха. Также поблизости находятся торговый центр Zenia Boulevard, престижные поля для гольфа и основные транспортные связи с городами Торревьеха и Ориуэла Коста.

Уникальная недвижимость, где эксклюзивность, комфорт и виды на море объединяются, создавая непревзойденное качество жизни.</ru><en>We present this stunning luxury penthouse located in the exclusive Sea Senses residential complex, one of the most sought-after developments in Punta Prima. With an unbeatable southeast orientation and panoramic views of the Mediterranean, this property offers a privileged seaside lifestyle.

The property features 2 bedrooms and 2 bathrooms, designed in a modern and functional layout to ensure maximum comfort. From the bright living room, you access a charming 12 m² terrace, perfect for enjoying the sunrise and the sea breeze. The highlight of this penthouse is its spectacular private 83 m² solarium, equipped with a jacuzzi and relaxation areas—an authentic private oasis with endless sea views, ideal for enjoying the Mediterranean climate all year round.

The property includes an underground parking space and a storage room, adding convenience and extra storage capacity.

Sea Senses is one of the most prestigious residential complexes on the Costa Blanca South, offering top-class communal areas with infinity pools facing the sea, a gym, spa, jacuzzis, sports courts, and landscaped spaces. A setting designed to provide privacy, luxury, and well-being.

Located in the renowned area of Punta Prima, this penthouse is just a few steps from the beach and surrounded by year-round services: supermarkets, restaurants, cafés, public transport, and leisure areas. It is also close to shopping centres such as Zenia Boulevard, prestigious golf courses, and main connections to Torrevieja and Orihuela Costa.

A truly unique home, where exclusivity, comfort, and sea views come together to offer an unparalleled living experience.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 12 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 9</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur/Este</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium (m2): 83</feature>
                <feature>Distance sea: 50</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a13df19f69_Drone Sea Senses WEBSITE 2048PX.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a13f01fd27_Drone Sea Senses WEBSITE 2048PX-4.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a1467e2d10_piscina nocturna.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb64bf75_benn05.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb666e76_benn06.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6785cc_benn08.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb637205_benn03.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6816c1_benn09.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6882fc_benn10.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6358d0_benn02.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb690f6f_benn11.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6973ac_benn12.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6a013b_benn13.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6a5fe5_benn14.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6af0be_benn15.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6b55c4_benn16.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6bebc8_benn17.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6d002d_benn18.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6cef94_benn19.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6df258_benn20.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6e028d_benn21.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/695f71550e88d_benn22_websize.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb6f0a03_benn23.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb70c5ef_benn25.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb71ab50_benn26.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb726a98_benn27.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb72bbe7_benn28.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb737cba_benn29.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb745bab_benn30.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb752424_benn31.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/695f7154f1190_benn33_websize.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/695f7155003b6_benn32_websize.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb7662ef_benn34.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb773500_benn35.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb7767ea_benn36.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb783497_benn37.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/69525eb786ea6_benn38.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a14582bd2f_034RefTomasz.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a141d04ee0_00 (6).jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="40">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a142491986_00 (9).jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="41">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a1430633b2_00 (11).jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="42">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a143d30664_00 (22).jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="43">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a144c8c953_00 (49).jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="44">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a1467e0bda_Holiday_Apartamento_alquiler_Punta Prima_SeaSenses (44).jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="45">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4205/692a143d3471b_00 (23).jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3513</id>
            <date>2025-11-28 22:36:31</date>
            <ref>4206</ref>
            <price>765000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Penthouse</type>
            <town>Torrevieja</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.944772200000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.706290000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Punta Prima</location_detail>
            <beds>3</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>139</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>C</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/penthouse/tid4206</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/atico/tid4206</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/penthouse/tid4206</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/pentkhausy/tid4206</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Presentamos este magnífico ático de 3 dormitorios y 2 baños con 139 m², ubicado en el prestigioso residencial Panorama Mar, uno de los complejos más modernos y valorados de Punta Prima. Situado en primera línea, ofrece impresionantes vistas abiertas al Mediterráneo y un entorno privilegiado para quienes buscan calidad, confort y exclusividad junto al mar.

La vivienda cuenta con una amplia y luminosa terraza de 28 m² orientada al sur, perfecta para disfrutar del sol durante todo el día, así como de la brisa marina y de unas vistas panorámicas incomparables. Su distribución interior es moderna y funcional, con estancias espaciosas, llenas de luz natural y diseñadas para maximizar el confort.

El ático incluye plaza de parking subterráneo y trastero, proporcionando comodidad adicional y espacio extra de almacenamiento.

Panorama Mar es un moderno complejo en primera línea que destaca por sus amplias piscinas, incluyendo una piscina climatizada, zonas ajardinadas y áreas de relax con vistas al mar. Ofrece un ambiente exclusivo, seguro y cuidado, ideal para disfrutar del estilo de vida mediterráneo durante todo el año.

Ubicado en una de las zonas más privilegiadas de la Costa Blanca, Punta Prima combina tranquilidad y servicios. La propiedad se encuentra a pocos pasos de la playa y está rodeada de restaurantes, supermercados y opciones de ocio, además de estar muy cerca de Zenia Boulevard y varios campos de golf de prestigio.</es><fr>Nous vous présentons ce magnifique penthouse de 3 chambres et 2 salles de bains de 139 m², situé dans le prestigieux complexe résidentiel Panorama Mar, l’un des plus modernes et les plus prisés de Punta Prima. Situé en première ligne, il offre de superbes vues ouvertes sur la Méditerranée et un cadre privilégié pour ceux qui recherchent qualité, confort et exclusivité en bord de mer.

Le logement dispose d’une spacieuse terrasse de 28 m² orientée au sud, idéale pour profiter du soleil toute la journée, de la brise marine et de vues panoramiques incomparables. L’agencement intérieur est moderne et fonctionnel, avec de grandes pièces baignées de lumière naturelle et conçues pour maximiser le confort.

Le penthouse comprend une place de parking souterrain et un cellier, offrant commodité et espace de rangement supplémentaire.

Panorama Mar est un complexe moderne en première ligne qui se distingue par ses grandes piscines, dont une piscine chauffée, ses espaces paysagers et ses zones de détente avec vue sur la mer. Il offre un environnement exclusif, sécurisé et bien entretenu, idéal pour profiter du style de vie méditerranéen toute l’année.

Situé dans l’une des zones les plus privilégiées de la Costa Blanca, Punta Prima allie tranquillité et commodités. La propriété se trouve à quelques pas de la plage et est entourée de restaurants, supermarchés et options de loisirs, tout en étant très proche de Zenia Boulevard et de plusieurs parcours de golf prestigieux.
</fr><ru>Представляем этот великолепный пентхаус с 3 спальнями и 2 ванными комнатами площадью 139 м², расположенный в престижном жилом комплексе Панорама-Мар, одном из самых современных и высоко оцененных комплексов в Пунта-Прима. Находясь на первой линии, он открывает потрясающие виды на Средиземное море и предлагает привилегированное расположение для тех, кто ценит качество, комфорт и эксклюзивность у моря.

Квартира имеет просторную и светлую террасу площадью 28 м² с южной ориентацией, идеально подходящую для того, чтобы наслаждаться солнцем в течение всего дня, морским бризом и непревзойденными панорамными видами. Планировка современная и функциональная, с просторными комнатами, наполненными естественным светом, созданными для максимального комфорта.

Пентхаус включает подземное парковочное место и кладовую, что обеспечивает дополнительное удобство и место для хранения.

Панорама-Мар — это современный комплекс на первой линии, который выделяется своими большими бассейнами, включая бассейн с подогревом, озеленёнными территориями и зонами для отдыха с видом на море. Комплекс предлагает эксклюзивную, безопасную и ухоженную среду, идеально подходящую для жизни в средиземноморском стиле круглый год.

Расположенный в одном из самых престижных районов Коста-Бланки, Пунта-Прима сочетает в себе спокойствие и удобство. Квартира находится в нескольких шагах от пляжа, в окружении ресторанов, супермаркетов и зон отдыха, а также недалеко от Zenia Boulevard и нескольких престижных полей для гольфа.</ru><en>We present this magnificent 3-bedroom, 2-bathroom penthouse with 139 m², located in the prestigious Panorama Mar residential complex, one of the most modern and highly regarded developments in Punta Prima. Situated frontline, it offers stunning open views of the Mediterranean and a privileged setting for those seeking quality, comfort, and exclusivity by the sea.

The property features a spacious and bright 28 m² south-facing terrace, perfect for enjoying the sun all day, the sea breeze, and unbeatable panoramic views. The interior layout is modern and functional, with generous rooms filled with natural light, designed to maximize comfort.

The penthouse includes an underground parking space and a storage room, providing additional convenience and extra storage.

Panorama Mar is a modern frontline complex that stands out for its large swimming pools, including a heated pool, landscaped areas, and relaxation zones with sea views. It offers an exclusive, secure, and well-maintained environment, ideal for enjoying the Mediterranean lifestyle all year round.

Located in one of the most privileged areas of the Costa Blanca, Punta Prima combines tranquility and convenience. The property is just a few steps from the beach and surrounded by restaurants, supermarkets, and leisure options, while being very close to Zenia Boulevard and several prestigious golf courses.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 28 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 9</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: 50</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/692a190ca4f79_126_web_PanoramaMar.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/692a18a2c070f_129_web_PanoramaMar.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/692a1941a7d00_128_web_PanoramaMar.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612c89777_bennec09.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612c87ccc_bennec08.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612cdf30a_bennec17.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612cf0e78_bennec18.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612ca5e93_bennec10.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612c9c6dd_bennec11.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612ccca2c_bennec15.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612ccb61a_bennec14.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612caeb7c_bennec12.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612cb99a0_bennec13.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612c54e13_bennec05.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612c69391_bennec06.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612c6ab49_bennec07.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612cf2365_bennec19.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d0ea2c_bennec20.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d0faf2_bennec21.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d2c0b8_bennec22.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d21966_bennec23.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d33a68_bennec24.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d3eb40_bennec25.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d4583b_bennec26.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d5c2c2_bennec27.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d57635_bennec28.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d6d7df_bennec30.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d7e65c_bennec32.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d8cd17_bennec33.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d8f7fb_bennec34.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612d9e8a7_bennec35.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612da0be8_bennec36.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612dafb8b_bennec37.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612db1bc5_bennec38.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612dcbbf6_bennec39.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/692a18a33375e_132_web_PanoramaMar.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/692a18a2c4622_130_web_PanoramaMar.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/692a18a31ee74_131_web_PanoramaMar.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612dc84d2_bennec40.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="40">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612de6dda_bennec41.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="41">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612de17d0_bennec42.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="42">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612e02585_bennec43.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="43">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612e0fa7b_bennec44.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="44">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612e15d38_bennec45.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="45">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612e2349e_bennec46.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="46">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612e341e1_bennec47.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="47">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612e37774_bennec48.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="48">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612e484b9_bennec49.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="49">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/6952612e4b6e9_bennec50.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="50">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4206/692d53874aeb6_4206 Plano.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3567</id>
            <date>2025-12-18 16:37:08</date>
            <ref>4208</ref>
            <price>765000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Apartment</type>
            <town>Torrevieja</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.943613000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.706550000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Punta Prima</location_detail>
            <beds>2</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>122</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>B</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/apartments/tid4208</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/apartamentos/tid4208</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/appartements/tid4208</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/kvartiry/tid4208</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Este exclusivo apartamento en quinta planta se ubica en el prestigioso residencial Posidonia, en primera línea de mar en Punta Prima. Originalmente proyectado con tres dormitorios, la vivienda fue modificada sobre plano para ofrecer 94 m² de puro confort, distribuidos ahora en dos amplios dormitorios y dos baños, ganando así una amplitud excepcional en las zonas de día.

Su punto fuerte es la doble orientación y sus espacios exteriores: una terraza de 16m² con vistas despejadas al mar y la bahía de Torrevieja, y una segunda terraza trasera de 12m2 con orientación sur y vistas hacia La Manga, garantizando sol, luz natural y ventilación cruzada durante todo el día.

La propiedad se entrega totalmente amueblada, con plaza de garaje subterránea y trastero incluidos. El complejo cuenta con zonas comunes de alto standing y seguridad. Ubicado a pie de servicios, supermercados y calas, se encuentra a aproximadamente 45 minutos del Aeropuerto de Alicante, conectando lujo y comodidad en una de las zonas más demandadas de la Costa Blanca.</es><fr>Cet appartement exclusif au cinquième étage est situé dans le prestigieux complexe résidentiel Posidonia, en première ligne de mer à Punta Prima. Initialement conçu avec trois chambres, le logement a été modifié sur plan pour offrir 94 m² de pur confort, répartis désormais en deux chambres spacieuses et deux salles de bains, offrant ainsi une amplitude exceptionnelle dans les pièces de vie.

Son point fort réside dans sa double orientation et ses espaces extérieurs : une terrasse de 16 m² avec vue dégagée sur la mer et la baie de Torrevieja, et une seconde terrasse arrière de 12 m² orientée sud avec vue vers La Manga, garantissant soleil, lumière naturelle et ventilation croisée tout au long de la journée.

La propriété est vendue entièrement meublée, avec une place de parking souterrain et un débarras inclus. Le complexe dispose d'espaces communs de haut standing et de sécurité. Situé à distance de marche des services, supermarchés et criques, il se trouve à environ 45 minutes de l'aéroport d'Alicante, alliant luxe et confort dans l'une des zones les plus prisées de la Costa Blanca.</fr><ru>Эти эксклюзивные апартаменты на пятом этаже расположены в престижном жилом комплексе Posidonia, на первой линии моря в Пунта-Прима. Изначально спроектированное с тремя спальнями, жилье было модифицировано на этапе строительства, чтобы предложить 94 м² чистого комфорта. Теперь оно включает две просторные спальни и две ванные комнаты, что обеспечило исключительный простор в дневных зонах.

Главным преимуществом является двойная ориентация и открытые пространства: терраса площадью 16 м² с панорамным видом на море и бухту Торревьехи, и вторая задняя терраса площадью 12 м² с южной ориентацией и видом на Ла-Мангу, что гарантирует солнце, естественное освещение и сквозную вентиляцию в течение всего дня.

Недвижимость продается полностью меблированной, включая место в подземном паркинге и кладовую. Комплекс располагает зонами общего пользования высокого уровня и системой безопасности. Апартаменты находятся в пешей доступности от всех сервисов, супермаркетов и бухт, примерно в 45 минутах от аэропорта Аликанте, сочетая роскошь и удобство в одном из самых востребованных районов Коста Бланки.</ru><en>This exclusive 5th-floor apartment is located in the prestigious Posidonia residential complex, on the seafront in Punta Prima. Originally designed with three bedrooms, the property was modified off-plan to offer 94 m² of pure comfort, now distributed into two spacious bedrooms and two bathrooms, gaining exceptional spaciousness in the living areas.

Its key strength lies in its double orientation and outdoor spaces: a 16 m² terrace with unobstructed views of the sea and the bay of Torrevieja, and a second 12 m² rear terrace facing south with views towards La Manga, guaranteeing sun, natural light, and cross ventilation throughout the day.

The property is sold fully furnished, with an underground parking space and storage room included. The complex features high-standard common areas and security. Located within walking distance of amenities, supermarkets, and coves, it is approximately 45 minutes from Alicante Airport, combining luxury and comfort in one of the most sought-after areas of the Costa Blanca.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 16 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 5</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Norte/Sur</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: No</feature>
                
                <feature>Distance sea: 50</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035bba4c5_be15.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b83f3b_be11.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b968b4_be12.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b9f1e3_be13.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c04150_be21.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b8ee4c_be10.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035bc6010_be16.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035bd7571_be18.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035be5bb8_be19.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b63c1a_be06.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035bcac5d_be17.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c79794_T73A0064.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035bea577_be20.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b73096_be09.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035ba7d50_be14.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b74090_be08.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b3f823_be03.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b627cc_be07.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b45b42_be04.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035b519cd_be05.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035e6ba23_T73A0246.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c17596_be23.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c086ba_be22.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c1aada_be24.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c279cc_be25.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c2ae7b_be26.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c37d1c_be27.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c3a8d5_be28.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c478e5_be29.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c4aa30_be30.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d9a3eb_T73A0160.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d29db3_T73A0140.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035cc21bb_T73A0130.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035cd4c87_T73A0132.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035e98e7c_T73A0251.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035e7de2d_T73A0250.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035c73861_T73A0065.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035ca690e_T73A0124.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035cd33bb_T73A0133.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="40">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035ce6f7f_T73A0135.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="41">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d0d875_T73A0137.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="42">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d0f0e4_T73A0138.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="43">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d2b4fb_T73A0141.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="44">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d3e0f7_T73A0142.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="45">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d3cc18_T73A0145.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="46">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d5021f_T73A0148.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="47">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d5b345_T73A0149.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="48">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d63378_T73A0151.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="49">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d6d9a1_T73A0154.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="50">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4208/6961035d7feca_T73A0156.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3584</id>
            <date>2026-01-09 15:23:58</date>
            <ref>4209RV</ref>
            <price>215000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Townhouse</type>
            <town>Orihuela</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.931894000000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.773076000000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Orihuela Costa</location_detail>
            <beds>2</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>83</built>
                <plot>25</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>D</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/townhouses/tid4209RV</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/adosados/tid4209RV</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/maisons-de-villes/tid4209RV</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/tounkhausy/tid4209RV</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Esta vivienda adosada en Lomas de Campoamor destaca por su orientación suroeste y su excelente aprovechamiento de los espacios exteriores, diseñados para disfrutar del sol de tarde y los atardeceres. Con 83 m² de vivienda, ofrece una distribución funcional de 2 dormitorios y 2 baños, encontrándose en buen estado de conservación y equipada con aire acondicionado.

El valor diferencial de la propiedad reside en sus tres zonas al aire libre: una parcela de 25 m² en la entrada, un porche trasero de 15 m² y un solárium de 33 m² en la cubierta, que ofrece vistas despejadas y directas al campo de golf.

La urbanización dispone de zonas verdes y una gran piscina comunitaria. Su ubicación es estratégica para el golfista y el residente vacacional: a tan solo 500 metros del Real Club de Golf Campoamor y colindante a zonas comerciales con supermercados y restaurantes, ofreciendo todos los servicios a pie sin sacrificar la tranquilidad del entorno.</es><fr>Cette maison mitoyenne à Lomas de Campoamor se distingue par son orientation sud-ouest et ses excellents espaces extérieurs, conçus pour profiter du soleil de l'après-midi et des couchers de soleil. Avec 83 m² habitables, elle offre une distribution fonctionnelle de 2 chambres et 2 salles de bains, le tout en bon état de conservation et équipé de la climatisation.

La valeur ajoutée de la propriété réside dans ses trois espaces en plein air : une parcelle de 25 m² à l'entrée, un porche arrière de 15 m² et un solarium de 33 m² sur le toit, offrant des vues dégagées et directes sur le terrain de golf.

L'urbanisation dispose d'espaces verts et d'une grande piscine commune. Son emplacement est stratégique pour les golfeurs et les résidents : à seulement 500 mètres du Real Club de Golf Campoamor et à proximité immédiate des zones commerciales avec supermarchés et restaurants, offrant tous les services à pied sans sacrifier la tranquillité des lieux.</fr><ru>Этот таунхаус в Lomas de Campoamor выделяется своей юго-западной ориентацией и великолепными открытыми зонами, идеально подходящими для наслаждения послеполуденным солнцем и закатами. Жилая площадь составляет 83 м² и включает 2 спальни и 2 ванные комнаты. Дом находится в хорошем состоянии и оборудован кондиционером.

Главным преимуществом недвижимости являются три открытые зоны: участок площадью 25 м² при входе, задняя веранда площадью 15 м² и просторный солярий на крыше площадью 33 м², откуда открывается прямой панорамный вид на поле для гольфа.

В урбанизации есть зеленые зоны и большой общий бассейн. Расположение стратегически удобно как для игроков в гольф, так и для отдыхающих: всего в 500 метрах от гольф-клуба Real Club de Golf Campoamor и рядом с коммерческой зоной с супермаркетами и ресторанами, что позволяет пользоваться всеми услугами пешком, сохраняя при этом спокойствие окружающей среды.</ru><en>This townhouse in Lomas de Campoamor stands out for its southwest orientation and excellent use of outdoor spaces, designed to enjoy the afternoon sun and sunsets. With 83 m² of living space, it offers a functional layout of 2 bedrooms and 2 bathrooms, is in good condition, and comes equipped with air conditioning.

The property's key value lies in its three outdoor areas: a 25 m² garden plot at the entrance, a 15 m² rear porch, and a 33 m² rooftop solarium, offering unobstructed direct views of the golf course.

The complex features green areas and a large communal swimming pool. Its location is strategic for golfers and holidaymakers alike: just 500 meters from the Real Club de Golf Campoamor and adjacent to commercial areas with supermarkets and restaurants, offering all amenities within walking distance without sacrificing the tranquility of the surroundings.</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 15 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: </feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur/Oeste</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium (m2): 33</feature>
                <feature>Distance sea: 4000</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147268e40a_IMG_9077.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614725e605b_IMG_9065.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147244f813_IMG_9025.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147246af38_IMG_9026.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614724693d0_IMG_9029.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472485440_IMG_9030.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614724a541d_IMG_9033.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147248da1b_IMG_9031.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614724a6f66_IMG_9032.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472590d28_IMG_9057.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614725a7e30_IMG_9059.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472450f5e_IMG_9024.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472433e6b_IMG_9015.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614725c0489_IMG_9063.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472414436_IMG_9011.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147241a563_IMG_9012.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614724bec36_IMG_9034.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614724c02ab_IMG_9035.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614724dfebc_IMG_9037.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472501f8a_IMG_9040.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147250fabf_IMG_9041.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147252763b_IMG_9043.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472529737_IMG_9044.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472547b11_IMG_9046.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147254624e_IMG_9048.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147255f63a_IMG_9049.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472569867_IMG_9051.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147257bf8f_IMG_9054.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147257fb64_IMG_9055.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614725ec021_IMG_9066.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614725b87b0_IMG_9062.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147261295c_IMG_9067.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147261e0f0_IMG_9068.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="34">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147263b9d8_IMG_9069.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="35">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614726356f9_IMG_9070.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="36">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147265449b_IMG_9073.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="37">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472656bc1_IMG_9074.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="38">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/696147266c91c_IMG_9075.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="39">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/69614726799e9_IMG_9076.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="40">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4209RV/6961472690dd5_IMG_9078.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property><property>
             <id>3586</id>
            <date>2026-01-12 14:22:52</date>
            <ref>4210</ref>
            <price>299000</price>
            <currency>EUR</currency>
            <price_freq>sale</price_freq>
            <part_ownership>0</part_ownership>
            <leasehold>0</leasehold>
            <new_build>0</new_build>
            <type>Apartment</type>
            <town>Orihuela Costa</town>
            <province>Alicante</province>
            <country>spain</country>
                <location>
                    <latitude>37.934002700000</latitude>
                    <longitude>-0.778116500000</longitude>
                </location><location_detail>Campoamor</location_detail>
            <beds>2</beds><baths>2</baths><pool>0</pool>
            <surface_area>
                <built>87</built>
                <plot>0</plot>
            </surface_area>
            <energy_rating>
                <consumption>F</consumption>
                <emissions>X</emissions>
            </energy_rating>
            <url>
                <en>https://bennecke.com/en/properties/apartments/tid4210</en>
                <es>https://www.bennecke.com/propiedades/apartamentos/tid4210</es>
                <fr>https://www.bennecke.com/fr/proprietes/appartements/tid4210</fr>
                <ru>https://www.bennecke.com/ru/nedvizhimost/kvartiry/tid4210</ru>
            </url><desc><es>Este espectacular ático en la exclusiva zona de Lomas de Campoamor ofrece una combinación perfecta de lujo y confort con sus 87 m² de vivienda en excelente estado y un impresionante solárium privado de 52 m² equipado con cocina propia para disfrutar de cenas inolvidables frente al Mediterráneo mientras se contempla el atardecer en un entorno de máxima privacidad

La propiedad cuenta con 2 amplios dormitorios con armarios empotrados y 2 baños completos con acabados de calidad destacando su luminosa orientación sur que garantiza sol durante todo el día además de una magnífica terraza acristalada que se encuentra totalmente unida al salón ampliando el espacio de vida y creando un ambiente diáfano y acogedor que permite deleitarse con las vistas despejadas al mar desde el interior de la vivienda en cualquier época del año

Situada estratégicamente junto al prestigioso campo de golf y a tan solo 3 km de las paradisíacas playas de la zona la vivienda dispone de todas las comodidades modernas como sistema de aire acondicionado frío y calor junto con una plaza de garaje incluida en el precio

Todo ello se ubica dentro de una urbanización privada de alto nivel que cuenta con servicios de seguridad permanente control de accesos y cámaras de vigilancia para su total tranquilidad y la de su familia representando una oportunidad única tanto para residencia habitual como para una inversión segura en una de las áreas más demandadas y cuidadas de la Costa Blanca donde el silencio y la exclusividad se fusionan con la cercanía a todos los servicios necesarios como centros comerciales restaurantes y zonas de ocio de primer nivel</es><fr>Ce spectaculaire attique dans le quartier exclusif de Lomas de Campoamor offre une combinaison parfaite de luxe et de confort avec ses 87 m² de surface habitable en excellent état et un impressionnant solarium privé de 52 m² équipé de sa propre cuisine pour profiter de dîners inoubliables face à la Méditerranée tout en contemplant le coucher du soleil dans un environnement de totale intimité

La propriété dispose de 2 grandes chambres avec placards intégrés et de 2 salles de bain complètes avec des finitions de qualité soulignant sa lumineuse orientation sud qui garantit un ensoleillement tout au long de la journée en plus d'une magnifique terrasse vitrée entièrement intégrée au salon agrandissant l'espace de vie et créant une ambiance ouverte et chaleureuse qui permet de profiter des vues dégagées sur la mer depuis l'intérieur de la maison en toute saison

Située stratégiquement à côté du prestigieux terrain de golf et à seulement 3 km des plages paradisiaques de la région la propriété dispose de tout le confort moderne comme un système de climatisation réversible chaud et froid ainsi qu'une place de garage incluse dans le prix

Tout cela se trouve au sein d'une urbanisation privée de haut standing qui bénéficie de services de sécurité permanente avec contrôle d'accès et caméras de surveillance pour votre totale tranquillité et celle de votre famille représentant une opportunité unique aussi bien pour une résidence habituelle que pour un investissement sûr dans l'un des secteurs les plus demandés et les mieux entretenus de la Costa Blanca où le calme et l'exclusivité se fusionnent avec la proximité de tous les services nécessaires tels que les centres commerciaux les restaurants et les zones de loisirs de premier plan</fr><ru>Этот впечатляющий пентхаус в эксклюзивном районе Ломас де Кампоамор предлагает идеальное сочетание роскоши и комфорта с жилой площадью 87 м² в отличном состоянии и потрясающим частным солярием площадью 52 м² оборудованным собственной кухней для незабываемых ужинов на фоне Средиземного моря и созерцания закатов в обстановке максимальной приватности

В квартире есть 2 просторные спальни со встроенными шкафами и 2 полноценные ванные комнаты с качественной отделкой а светлая южная ориентация гарантирует солнце в течение всего дня в дополнение к великолепной застекленной террасе которая полностью объединена с гостиной расширяя жилое пространство и создавая уютную атмосферу позволяющую наслаждаться панорамным видом на море прямо из дома в любое время года

Расположенный в стратегическом месте рядом с престижным полем для гольфа и всего в 3 км от райских пляжей этого района дом оснащен всеми современными удобствами включая систему кондиционирования воздуха зима-лето а также место в гараже включенное в стоимость

Все это находится на территории закрытой урбанизации высокого уровня которая располагает круглосуточной службой охраны контролем доступа и камерами видеонаблюдения для вашего полного спокойствия и безопасности вашей семьи представляя собой уникальную возможность как для постоянного проживания так и для надежных инвестиций в одном из самых востребованных и ухоженных районов Коста-Бланки где тишина и эксклюзивность сочетаются с близостью ко всей необходимой инфраструктуре такой как торговые центры рестораны и первоклассные зоны отдыха</ru><en>This spectacular penthouse in the exclusive area of Lomas de Campoamor offers a perfect combination of luxury and comfort with its 87 m² of living space in excellent condition and an impressive 52 m² private solarium equipped with its own kitchen to enjoy unforgettable dinners facing the Mediterranean while contemplating the sunset in an environment of maximum privacy

The property features 2 large bedrooms with fitted wardrobes and 2 full bathrooms with quality finishes highlighting its bright south orientation which guarantees sun all day long as well as a magnificent glass-enclosed terrace that is fully integrated into the living room expanding the living space and creating a bright and welcoming open-plan atmosphere that allows you to enjoy the unobstructed sea views from inside the home at any time of the year

Strategically located next to the prestigious golf course and just 3 km from the paradisiacal beaches of the area the property has all modern amenities such as air conditioning with hot and cold air system along with a parking space included in the price

All this is located within a high-level private urbanization that features permanent security services access control and surveillance cameras for your total peace of mind and that of your family representing a unique opportunity for both a permanent residence or a secure investment in one of the most sought-after and well-maintained areas of the Costa Blanca where silence and exclusivity merge with the proximity to all necessary services such as shopping centers restaurants and top-level leisure areas</en></desc>
            <features>
                <feature>Terrace (m2): 11.81 </feature>
                <feature>Floor: 3</feature>
                <feature>Orientation: Sur</feature>
                <feature>Furnished: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Garage: No</feature>
                <feature>Storage: No</feature>
                <feature>Underground Parking: No</feature>
                <feature>Solarium: Yes</feature>
                <feature>Solarium (m2): 51</feature>
                <feature>Distance sea: 3000</feature>
            </features>
            <notes>00</notes>
            <images><image id="1">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e37b533_IMG_9133.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="2">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e370db7_IMG_9135.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="3">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e38c050_IMG_9136.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="4">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e391dad_IMG_9137.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="5">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e4119b7_IMG_9147.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="6">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e3bf269_IMG_9141.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="7">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e3ea547_IMG_9145.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="8">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e3bc9c0_IMG_9142.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="9">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e3cdea9_IMG_9143.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="10">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e3db9e9_IMG_9144.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="11">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e402dd5_IMG_9146.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="12">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e4142a7_IMG_9148.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="13">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e42dc0e_IMG_9149.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="14">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e42fa20_IMG_9150.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="15">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e44a34d_IMG_9151.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="16">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e44087a_IMG_9153.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="17">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e45b738_IMG_9155.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="18">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e46e624_IMG_9156.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="19">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e47709d_IMG_9157.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="20">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e48a9b7_IMG_9158.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="21">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e492a88_IMG_9159.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="22">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e4a6fba_IMG_9160.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="23">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e452dee_IMG_9154.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="24">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e4aed79_IMG_9161.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="25">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e4b8d33_IMG_9162.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="26">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e4ca040_IMG_9163.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="27">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e4cb08a_IMG_9164.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="28">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e4e6618_IMG_9165.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="29">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e4e7687_IMG_9166.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="30">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e504cc9_IMG_9167.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="31">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e505f02_IMG_9168.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="32">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e3a9347_IMG_9138.jpg</url>
                    </image><image id="33">
                        <url>https://api.bennecke.com/uploads/reference/4210/6967d4e3a3997_IMG_9140.jpg</url>
                    </image>
            </images>
            <prime></prime>
            </property></root>